<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quotes Bank</string>
    <string name="pop_heading">Would Like to Send You Notifications.</string>
    <string name="pop_details">Notification may include alerts,
    sounds and icon badges. These can\'t be configured in Setting </string>
    <string name="pop_dont">Don\'t Allow</string>
    <string name="pop_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="select">Select Your Interest</string>
    <string name="bed1">At quotebank, we think everyone</string>
    <string name="bed2">Please enter what time you</string>
    <string name="bed3">motivational note.</string>
    <string name="bed4">Notifications will be sent to you 10</string>
    <string name="bed5">minutes after you wake up and 10</string>
    <string name="bed6">minutes before you sleep.</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>


    <!--Arts Quotes-->
    <string-array name="art_Quotes">
        <item>"Do not fear mistakes - there are none." </item>
        <item>"A man paints with his brains and not with his hands." </item>
        <item>"In our time there are many artists who do something because it is new; they see their value and their justification in this newness. They are deceiving themselves; novelty is seldom the essential. This has to do with one thing only; making a subject better from its intrinsic nature." </item>
        <item>"You come to nature with all her theories, and she knocks them all flat." </item>
        <item>"The emotions are sometimes so strong that I work without knowing it. The strokes come like speech." </item>
        <item>"If I were called upon to define briefly the word Art, I should call it the reproduction of what the senses preceive in nature, seen through the veil of the soul." </item>
        <item>"If you always do what you always did - you\'ll always get what you always got." </item>
        <item>"Life is the art of drawing without an eraser." </item>
        <item>"The object isn’t to make art, it’s to be in that wonderful state which makes art inevitable." </item>
        <item>"Art is a collaboration between God and the artist, and the less the artist does the better." </item>
        <item>"I invent nothing, I rediscover." </item>
        <item>"I would rather die of passion than of boredom." </item>
        <item>"Every artist dips his brush in his own soul, and paints his own nature into his pictures." </item>
        <item>"Art Is Anything You Can Get Away With." </item>
        <item>"Action Is The Foundational Key To All Success." </item>
        <item>"Creativity Takes Courage." </item>
        <item>"If We Go For The Easy Way, We Never Change." </item>
        <item>"Art Should Be Something That Liberates Your Soul." </item>
        <item>"I Paint Flowers So They Will Not Die." </item>
        <item>"You Get Whatever Accomplishment You Are Willing To Declare." </item>
        <item>"It Doesn’t Matter How The Paint Is Put On, As Long As Something Is Said." </item>
        <item>"Amateurs Look For Inspiration, The Rest Of Us Just Get Up And Go To Work." </item>
        <item>"If I Knew What The Picture Was Going To Be Like, I Wouldn’t Make It." </item>
        <item>"Have No Fear Of Perfection, You’ll Never Reach It." </item>
        <item>"The Most Interesting Thing About Artists Is How They Live." </item>
        <item>"I Don’t Think About Art When I’m Working. I Try To Think About Life." </item>
        <item>"Great Things Are Done By A Series Of Small Things Brought Together." </item>
        <item>"Every Artists Dips Her Brush Into Her Own Soul, And Paints Her Own Truth Into Her Pictures." </item>
        <item>"Art Is To Console Those Who Are Broken By Life." </item>
        <item>"Inhale Possibility, Exhale Creativity." </item>
        <item>"Go Out And Paint The Stars." </item>
        <item>"Go To Your Studio And Make Stuff." </item>
        <item>"There Are No Rules To Creativity." </item>
        <item>"Art Is An Adventure Into An  World, Which Can Be Explored Only By Those Willing To Take Risks." </item>
        <item>"You Were Born To Make Art." </item>
        <item>"Art Should Disturb The Comfortable And Comfort The Disturbed." </item>
        <item>"I Aspire To Inspire Before I Expire." </item>
        <item>"I Have Been Absolutely Terrified Every Moment Of My Life – And I Have Never Let It Keep Me From Doing A Single Thing I Wanted To Do." </item>
        <item>"If You Don’t Do It Someone Else Will." </item>
        <item>"Art Is My Life And My Life Is Art." </item>
        <item>"I Make Art To Show My Soul That I Am Listening." </item>
        <item>"The Creative Process Is A Process Of Surrender, Not Control." </item>
        <item>"The Most Beautiful Thing We Can Experience Is The Mystery." </item>
        <item>"You Are Your Only Limit." </item>
        <item>"He Who Works With His Hands Is A Laborer. He Who Works With His Hands And His Head Is A Craftsman. He Who Works With His Hands And His Head And His Heart Is An Artist." </item>
        <item>"Art Is An Experience, Not An Object." </item>
        <item>"Creative Isn’t The Way I Think, It’s The Way I Like To Live." </item>
        <item>"The Creative Person Is Both More Primitive And More Cultivated, More Destructive, A Lot Madder And A Lot Saner, Than The Average Person." </item>
        <item>"Who Says That My Dreams Have To Stay Just My Dreams?" </item>
        <item>"There Is No Must In Art Because Art Is Free." </item>
        <item>"Do More Than Just Exist." </item>
        <item>"I’m Not The Average Girl From Your Video And I Ain’t Built Like A Supermodel But I Learned To Love Myself Unconditionally Because I Am A Queen." </item>
        <item>"It Isn’t Until The Painter Has No Idea What He’s Doing That He Makes Good Paintings." </item>
        <item>"I Feel Glorious, Dynamic Energy. I Am Active And Alive." </item>
        <item>"Every Artist Was First An Amateur." </item>
        <item>"If There Is No Way, Create One." </item>
        <item>"I Was Created To Create." </item>
        <item>"No Artist Tolerates Reality." </item>
        <item>"Art Washes From The Soul The Dust Of Everyday Life." </item>
        <item>"Art Does Not Reproduce What You See. It Makes Us See." </item>
        <item>"Imagination Is More Important Than Knowledge." </item>
        <item>"I Shut My Eyes In Order To See." </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="art_author">
        <item>  Vincent van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Henri Matisse  </item>
        <item>  Edward Hopper  </item>
        <item>  Andy Warhol </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>   Marc Chagall  </item>
        <item>  Piet Mondrian  </item>
        <item>  Salvador Dali  </item>
        <item>   Francis Bacon  </item>
        <item>  Georgia O’Keeffe  </item>
        <item> Alberto Giacometti  </item>
        <item>   Auguste Rodin  </item>
        <item>   Berthe Morisot  </item>
        <item>  Henry Moore  </item>
        <item>  Jackson Pollock  </item>
        <item>  Edgar Degas  </item>
        <item>  Ralph Waldo Emerson  </item>
        <item>  Georgia O’Keeffe  </item>
        <item> Eugene Delacroix  </item>
        <item>  Marc Chagall  </item>
        <item>  Paul Cezanne  </item>
        <item>  Rene Magritte  </item>
        <item>  Marc Chagall  </item>
        <item>  Georgia O\'Keeffe  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Martin Kippenberger  </item>
        <item>  Andy Warhol  </item>
        <item>  Frida Kahlo  </item>
        <item>   Francis Bacon  </item>
        <item>  Paul Cezanne  </item>
        <item>  Salvador Dali  </item>
        <item>  Lucian Freud  </item>
        <item>   Wassily Kandinsky  </item>
        <item>  Leonardo da Vinci  </item>
        <item>  Michelangelo  </item>
        <item>  Claude Monet  </item>
        <item>   Edvard Munch  </item>
        <item>  John Olsen  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Banksy  </item>
        <item>  Twyla Tharp  </item>
        <item>  Charles Horton Cooley  </item>
        <item>  Henry Moore  </item>
        <item>  Leonardo da Vinci  </item>
        <item>  Paul Valéry  </item>
        <item>  Aristotle  </item>
        <item>  Oscar Wilde  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Stella Adler  </item>
        <item>   Schumann  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Leonardo da Vinci  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Michelangelo  </item>
        <item>  Georges Rouault  </item>
        <item>  Theodore Dreiser  </item>
        <item>  James mcneill Whistler  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Scott Adams  </item>
        <item>  Edgar Degas  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Paul Strand  </item>
        <item>  Henry David Thoreau  </item>
        <item>  Dr Suess  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>   Albrecht Durer  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Rembrandt  </item>
        <item>  Leonardo Da Vinci  </item>
        <item>  Kurt Vonnegut  </item>
        <item>  Mark Rothko  </item>
        <item>    </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Pablo Picasso  </item>
        <item>  Andy Warhol  </item>
        <item>  Robert Hughes  </item>
        <item>  Émile Zola  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Jean-Jacques Rousseau  </item>
        <item>  Paul Gardner  </item>
        <item>  George Moore  </item>
        <item>  Vincent van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Miles David  </item>
        <item>  Michelangelo  </item>
        <item>  Henri de Toulouse Lautrec  </item>
        <item>  Pierre Auguste Renoir  </item>
        <item>  Vincent Van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Paul Cezanne  </item>
        <item>   </item>
        <item>  - John W. Gardner  </item>
        <item>  - Robert Henri  </item>
        <item>  - Andre Gide  </item>
        <item>  Auguste Rodin  </item>
        <item>  Vincent van Gogh  </item>
        <item>  Henry Ward Beecher </item>
        <item>  – Andy Warhol </item>
        <item>  – Pablo Picasso </item>
        <item>  – Henri Matisse </item>
        <item>Marina Abramović </item>
        <item>  – Keith Haring </item>
        <item>  – Frida Kahlo </item>
        <item>  – Georgia O’keeffe </item>
        <item>  – Jackson Pollock </item>
        <item>  – Chuck Close </item>
        <item>  – Cindy Sherman </item>
        <item>Salvador Dalí </item>
        <item>Marcel Duchamp </item>
        <item>Jean-Michel Basquiat </item>
        <item>Vincent Van Gogh </item>
        <item>Datura </item>
        <item>Vincent Van Gogh </item>
        <item>Laura Jaworski </item>
        <item>Van Gogh </item>
        <item>Fred Babb </item>
        <item>Laura Jaworski </item>
        <item>Mark Rothko </item>
        <item>Anonymous </item>
        <item>Anonymous </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Georgia O’keeffe </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Yoko Ono </item>
        <item>Pat Wiederspan Jones </item>
        <item>Julia Cameron </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Anonymous </item>
        <item>St Francis Of Assisi </item>
        <item>Robert Motherwell </item>
        <item>Paul Sandip </item>
        <item>Frank Barron </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  – Wassily Kandinsky </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  – India Arie </item>
        <item>  – Edgar Degas </item>
        <item>  – Louise Hay </item>
        <item>  – Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  – Nietzsche </item>
        <item>   Pablo Picasso </item>
        <item>  – Paul Klee </item>
        <item>  – Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>  – Paul Gauguin </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Fitness Quotes-->
    <string-array name="fitness_Quotes">
        <item>"By exercise. I\'ll tell you one thing, you don\'t always have to be on go. I sit around a lot, I read a lot, and I do watch television. But I also work out for two hours every day of my life, even when I’m on the road." </item>
        <item>"A man\'s health can be judged by which he takes two at a time – pills or stairs." </item>
        <item>"Whether you think you can or whether you think you can\'t, you\'re right!" </item>
        <item>"He who does not mind his belly, will hardly mind anything else." </item>
        <item>"Never hurry. Take plenty of exercise. Always be cheerful. Take all the sleep you need. You may expect to be well." </item>
        <item>"Those who do not find time for exercise will have to find time for illness." </item>
        <item>"I wouldn\'t say anything is impossible. I think that everything is possible as long as you put your mind to it and put the work and time into it." </item>
        <item>"It is exercise alone that supports the spirits, and keeps the mind in vigor." </item>
        <item>"Money is the most envied, but the least enjoyed. Health is the most enjoyed, but the least envied." </item>
        <item>"It is remarkable how ones wits are sharpened by physical exercise." </item>
        <item>"Toughness is in the soul and spirit, not in muscles." </item>
        <item>"Movement is a medicine for creating change in a person"s physical, emotional, and mental states." </item>
        <item>"If you have health, you probably will be happy, and if you have health and happiness, you have all the wealth you need, even if it is not all you want." </item>
        <item>"Happiness lies, first of all, in health." </item>
        <item>"True enjoyment comes from activity of the mind and exercise of the body; the two are united." </item>
        <item>"The resistance that you fight physically in the gym and the resistance that you fight in life can only build a strong character." </item>
        <item>"If you don\'t do what\'s best for your body, you\'re the one who comes up on the short end." </item>
        <item>"When it comes to eating right and exercising, there is no"I\'ll start tomorrow." Tomorrow is disease."  </item>
        <item>"The greatest wealth is health." </item>
        <item>"Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself." </item>
        <item>"Take care of your body, then the rest will automatically become stronger." </item>
        <item>"A vigorous five-mile walk will do more good for an unhappy but otherwise healthy adult than all the medicine and psychology in the world." </item>
        <item>"Time and health are two precious assets that we don\'t recognize and appreciate until they have been depleted." </item>
        <item>"It\'s not whether you get knocked down; it\'s whether you get up." </item>
        <item>"If you always put limit on everything you do, physical or anything else. It will spread into your work and into your life. There are no limits. There are only plateaus, and you must not stay there, you must go beyond them." </item>
        <item>"Leave all the afternoon for exercise and recreation, which are as necessary as reading. I will rather say more necessary because health is worth more than learning." </item>
        <item>"The higher your energy level, the more efficient your body. The more efficient your body, the better you feel and the more you will use your talent to produce outstanding results." </item>
        <item>"Pain is temporary. Quitting lasts forever." </item>
        <item>"We do not stop exercising because we grow old – we grow old because we stop exercising." </item>
        <item>"I like weights. You know where you stand with them. Well, sometimes you\'re lying under them, trying not to let them crush you, but you see, you KNOW they\'d crush you if they could. There\'s honesty." </item>
        <item>"People say that losing weight is no walk in the park. When I hear that I think, yeah, that"s the problem." </item>
        <item>"Exercise is good for your mind, body, and soul." </item>
        <item>"Running is one the best solutions to a clear mind." </item>
        <item>"No matter how good you get you can always get better and that\'s the exciting part." </item>
        <item>"My goal has always been to help people help themselves. Your body is your most priceless possession; you\'ve go to take care of it!" </item>
        <item>"Physical fitness is not only one of the most important keys to a healthy body, it is the basis of dynamic and creative intellectual activity." </item>
        <item>"The last three or four reps is what makes the muscle grow. This area of pain divides the champion from someone else who is not a champion." </item>
        <item>"There\'s no secret formula. I lift heavy, work hard, and aim to be the best." </item>
        <item>"If something stands between you and your success, move it. Never be denied." </item>
        <item>"You have to push past your perceived limits, push past that point you thought was as far as you can go." </item>
        <item>"It is health that is real wealth and not the pieces of gold and silvers." </item>
        <item>"The real workout starts when you want to stop." </item>
        <item>"To be number one, you have to train like you\'re number two." </item>
        <item>"Everybody wants to be a bodybuilder, but nobody wants to lift no heavy-ass weights." </item>
        <item>"I hated every minute of training, but I said, ‘Don\'t quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion." </item>
        <item>"Obsessed is just a word the lazy use to describe the dedicated." </item>
        <item>"Get off the treadmill of consumption, replication, and mediocrity. Begin lifting the weights of creativity, originality, and success." </item>
        <item>"I\'d rather be the guy doing and failing than the guy doing nothing more than telling others they\'ve failed." </item>
        <item>"Most champions are built by punch the clock workouts rather than extraordinary efforts." </item>
        <item>"Training records become a barometer of accomplishment and a roadmap for further progress." </item>
        <item>"Sell yourself short on nutrition and you\'re selling yourself short on maximizing your physique development." </item>
        <item>"I train and I go home, and when I\'m home, I think about training. That\'s my life every day, and that\'s it." </item>
        <item>"What hurts today, makes you stronger tomorrow" </item>
        <item>"For me life is continuously being hungry. The meaning of life is not simply to exist, to survive, but to move ahead, to go up, to achieve, to conquer." </item>
        <item>"I do it as a therapy. I do it as something to keep me alive. We all need a little discipline. Exercise is my discipline." </item>
        <item>"When you get knocked down in life, do everything you can to fall on your back because if you can look up, you can get up." </item>
        <item>"A lot of guys have better genes but if you work hard and consistently, you can outperform them." </item>
        <item>"Being Negative and Lazy is a disease that leads to pain, hardship, depression, poor health and failure. Be proactive, and give a damn to achieve success!" </item>
        <item>"Each workout is like a brick in a building, and every time you go in there and do a half-ass workout, you\'re not laying a brick down. Somebody else is." </item>
        <item>"Blood, sweat and respect. First two you give, last one you earn." </item>
        <item>"Keep your blood clean, your body lean, and your mind sharp." </item>
        <item>"Success isn\'t always about greatness, It\'s about consistency. Consistent hard work gains success. GREATNESS will come." </item>
        <item>"Success is like anything worthwhile. It has a price. You have to pay the price to win and you have to pay the price to get to the point where success is possible. Most important, you must pay the price to stay there." </item>
        <item>"Strength does not come from winning. Your struggles develop your strengths. When you go through hardships and decide not to surrender, that is strength." </item>
        <item>"Rise and grind! Nothing comes to a sleeper but a dream!" </item>
        <item>"The best training program in the world is absolutely worthless without the will to execute it properly, consistently, and with intensity." </item>
        <item>"Your mind is the strongest and most valuable muscle you can grow in the gym." </item>
        <item>"Success at anything will always come down to this: focus and effort. And we control both." </item>
        <item>"Energy and persistence conquer all things." </item>
        <item>"Motivation will almost always beat mere talent." </item>
        <item>"I would like to be the first man in the gym business to throw out my scale. If you don\'t like what you see in the mirror, what difference does it make what the scale says?" </item>
        <item>"If you think lifting weights is dangerous, try being weak. Being weak is dangerous." </item>
        <item>"Your love for what you do and willingness to push yourself where others aren\'t prepared to go is what will make you great." </item>
        <item>"Ability is what you\'re capable of doing. Motivation determines what you do. Attitude determines how well you do it." </item>
        <item>"Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records." </item>
        <item>"A fit, healthy body—that is the best fashion statement." </item>
        <item>"Create a routine. If you take these two steps – setting aside the time and making your body move – three or four days per week, then you have in effect established a routine. It is this routine, this plan, this expectation of yourself that is going to give you the power to change the nature of your relationship with exercise." </item>
        <item>"The best day to start exercising is today. Tomorrow can turn into weeks, months or years." </item>
        <item>"Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen." </item>
        <item>"You would be surprised what two hours of daily exercise and five hundred stomach crunches can do for you." </item>
        <item>"Your health account, your bank account, they\'re the same thing. The more you put in, the more you can take out. Exercise is king and nutrition is queen. Together you have a kingdom." </item>
        <item>"The individual who says it is not possible should move out of the way of those doing it." </item>
        <item>"The miracle isn\'t that I finished. The miracle is that I had the courage to start." </item>
        <item>"If you\'re capable of sending a legible text message between sets, you probably aren\'t working hard enough." </item>
        <item>"A champion is someone who gets up when they can\'t." </item>
        <item>"The question isn\'t who is going to let me; it\'s who is going to stop me." </item>
        <item>"Getting more exercise isn\'t only good for your waistline. It\'s a natural anti-depressant, that leaves you in a great mood." </item>
        <item>"It\'s easier to stay in shape if you never let yourself get out of shape in the first place." </item>
        <item>"You dream. You plan. You reach. There will be obstacles. There will be doubters. There will be mistakes. But with hard work, with belief, with confidence and trust in yourself and those around you, there are no limits." </item>
        <item>"Getting fit is all about mind over matter. I don\'t mind, so it doesn\'t matter." </item>
        <item>"Stop making excuses and start giving yourself enough reasons why you must eat healthier and exercise regularly. Excuses are your enemies of progress." </item>
        <item>"If you aren\'t hurting after a good workout then obviously you haven\'t done something right." </item>
        <item>"Most people give up right before the big break comes—don\'t let that person be you." </item>
        <item>"There\'s more to life than training, but training is what puts more in your life." </item>
        <item>"Discipline is doing what you hate to do, but nonetheless doing it like you love it." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t measure yourself by what you have accomplished, but by what you should have accomplished with your ability." </item>
        <item>"At the end of the day, your health is your responsibility." </item>
        <item>"There are no shortcuts. The fact that a shortcut is important to you means that you are [lazy]." </item>
        <item>"To be precise, there are three gems for healthy life: sufficient workouts, healthy food, and enough sleep." </item>
        <item>"A healthy body is a platform for flourishing a healthy mind." </item>
        <item>"All Successes Begin With Self-Discipline. It Starts With You." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Success Isn\'t Always About Greatness, It\'s About Consistency. Consistent, Hard Work Gains Success. Greatness Will Come." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Some People Want It To Happen, Some Wish It Would Happen, Others Make It Happen." </item>
        <item>"Your Health Account, Your Bank Account, They\'re The Same Thing. The More You Put In, The More You Can Take Out. Exercise Is King And Nutrition Is Queen. Together You Have A Kingdom." </item>
        <item>"You Dream. You Plan. You Reach. There Will Be Obstacles. There Will Be Doubters. There Will Be Mistakes. But With Hard Work, With Belief, With Confidence And Trust In Yourself And Those Around You, There Are No Limits." </item>
        <item>"I Will Sacrifice Whatever Is Necessary To Be The Best." </item>
        <item>"Enjoy Your Day And Start It By Remembering Your Dreams, Your Goals And Your Achievements! Today Is Your Chance For Success." </item>
        <item>"Every Day You Are Reborn And You Have A Chance To Become The Person Who You Want To Be!" </item>
        <item>"Success Comes To Those Who Have The Will Power To Win Over Their Snooze Buttons." </item>
        <item>"15 Minutes A Day! Give Me Just This In Morning And I\'ll Prove I Can Make You A New Man." </item>
        <item>"Bodybuilding Is Much Like Any Other Sport. To Be Successful, You Must Dedicate Yourself 100% To Your Training, Diet And Mental Approach." </item>
        <item>"A Lot Of People Are Afraid Of Heights. Not Me, I\'m Afraid Of Widths." </item>
        <item>"If I Don\'t Feel Confident About My Body, I\'m Not Going To Sit At Home And Feel Sorry For Myself And Not Do Something About It. It\'s All About Taking Action And Not Being Lazy. So You Do The Work, Whether It\'s Fitness Or Whatever. It\'s About Getting Up, Motivating Yourself And Just Doing It." </item>
        <item>"The Mind Is The Most Important Part Of Achieving Any Fitness Goal. Mental Change Always Comes Before Physical Change." </item>
        <item>"For Me, Fitness Is Not Just About Hitting The Gym; It Is Also About An Inner Happiness And An Overall Well-Being. " </item>
        <item>"Fitness Is Not About Being Better Than Someone Else… It\'s About Being Better Than You Used To Be." </item>
        <item>"Time And Health Are Two Precious Assets That We Don\'t Recognize And Appreciate Until They Have Been Depleted." </item>
        <item>"To Enjoy The Glow Of Good Health, You Must Exercise." </item>
        <item>"Take Care Of Your Body. It\'s The Only Place You Have To Live." </item>
        <item>"Of Course I Want To Be Number One. But Being Happy &amp; Healthy Is The Most Important Thing." </item>
        <item>"One Workout At A Time. One Day At A Time. One Meal At A Time." </item>
        <item>"Stop Saying I Wish. Start Saying I Will." </item>
        <item>"A Healthy Outside Starts From The Inside." </item>
        <item>"Instead Of"I Don\'t Have Time" Try Saying "It\'s Not A Priority" And See How That Feels." </item>
        <item>"Your Body Is Your Most Priceless Possession. Take Care Of It." </item>
        <item>"Health Is Not Just About What You\'re Eating. It\'s Also About What You\'re Thinking And Saying." </item>
        <item>"The First Wealth Is Health." </item>
        <item>"A Strong Body Is Not Made In Comfort." </item>
        <item>"It Always Seems Impossible Until It Is Done." </item>
        <item>"Push Harder Than Yesterday If You Want A Different Tomorrow." </item>
        <item>"You Don\'t Have To Be Good At It, You Just Have To Do It." </item>
        <item>"We Do Today What They Wo\'t, So Tomorrow We Accomplish What They Can\'t." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"When You Walk Up To Opportunities Door, Don\'t Knock It… Kick That B!Tch In, Smile And Introduce Yourself." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Wake Up Determined. Go To Bed Satisfied." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Success Isn\'t An Overnight Thing. It\'s When Every Day You Get A Little Better Than The Day Before. It All Adds Up." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Think Back 5yrs Ago. Think Of Where You\'re At Today. Think Ahead 5 Years About What You Want To Accomplish. Be Unstoppable." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Success At Anything Will Always Come Down To This: Focus &amp; Effort, And We Control Both." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Be The Person That When Your Feet Touch The Floor In The Morning The Devil Says, "Awe Sh!T, They\'re Up!" </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"Nobody Is Perfect, So Get Over The Fear Of Being Or Doing Everything Perfectly. Besides, Perfect Is Boring." </item>
        <item>"We Must Appreciate And Never Underestimate Our Own Inner Power." </item>
        <item>"I Know That If I Set My Mind To Something, Even If People Are Saying I Can\'t Do It, I Will Achieve It." </item>
        <item>"To Keep Winning, I Have To Keep Improving." </item>
        <item>"I Was Never A Natural Athlete, But I Paid My Dues In Sweat And Concentration, And Took The Time Necessary To Learn Karate And Became A World Champion." </item>
        <item>"When You Have A Clear Vision Of Your Goal, It\'s Easier To Take The First Step Toward It." </item>
        <item>"If You Ain\'t Pissed Off For Greatness, That Just Means You\'re Okay With Being Mediocre." </item>
        <item>"You Have To Push Past Your Perceived Limits, Push Past That Point You Thought Was As Far As You Can Go." </item>
        <item>"You\'re Going To Have To Let It Hurt. Let It Suck. The Harder You Work, The Better You Will Look. Your Appearance Isn\'t Parallel To How Heavy You Lift, It\'s Parallel To How Hard You Work." </item>
        <item>"I Feel An Endless Need To Learn, To Improve, To Evolve—Not Only To Please The Coach And The Fans—But Also To Feel Satisfied With Myself." </item>
        <item>"Most People Give Up Right Before The Big Break Comes—Don\'t Let That Person Be You." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t Be Afraid Of Failure. This Is The Way To Succeed." </item>
        <item>"Success Is Usually The Culmination Of Controlling Failure." </item>
        <item>"There Comes A Certain Point In Life When You Have To Stop Blaming Other People For How You Feel Or The Misfortunes In Your Life. You Can\'t Go Through Life Obsessing About What Might Have Been." </item>
        <item>"If Something Stands Between You And Your Success, Move It. Never Be Denied." </item>
        <item>"The Rock" </item>
        <item>"There\'s No Secret Formula. I Lift Heavy, Work Hard, And Aim To Be The Best." </item>
        <item>"You Shall Gain, But You Shall Pay With Sweat, Blood, And Vomit." </item>
        <item>"In Training, You Listen To Your Body. In Competition, You Tell Your Body To Shut Up." </item>
        <item>"The Last Three Or Four Reps Is What Makes The Muscle Grow. This Area Of Pain Divides The Champion From Someone Else Who Is Not A Champion." </item>
        <item>"Behind Every Successful Woman Is The Butt She Got Moving To Get Her There…" </item>
        <item>"The Difference Between Your Body This Week &amp; Next Week Is What You Do For The Next Seven Days To Achieve Your Goals." </item>
        <item>"It\'s Actually Pretty Simple. Either You Do It, Or You Don\'t." </item>
        <item>"A Good Man Can Make You Feel Sexy, Strong And Able To Take On The World… Oh, Sorry… That\'s Exercise… Exercise Does That…" </item>
        <item>"One Of The Greatest Moments In Life Is Realizing That Two Weeks Ago, Your Body Couldn\'t Do What It Just Did." </item>
        <item>"The Hardest Lift Of All Is Lifting Your Butt Off The Couch." </item>
        <item>"Fit Is Not A Destination It Is A Way Of Life." </item>
        <item>"Making Excuses Burns Zero Calories Per Hour." </item>
        <item>"I Will Make Sweat My Best Accessory. I Will Run Harder Than My Mascara." </item>
        <item>"Sweat Is Just Fat Crying." </item>
        <item>"I Tried Every Diet In The Book. I Tried Some That Weren\'t In The Book. I Tried Eating The Book. It Tasted Better Than Most Of The Diets." </item>
        <item>"She Said"Gym Or Me". Sometimes I Miss Her." </item>
        <item>"I Forgot To Post On Facebook I Was Going To The Gym. Now This Whole Workout Was A Waste Of Time." </item>
        <item>"I Don\'t Always Go To The Gym. But When I Do…I Don\'t Know What The Hell I\'m Doing" </item>
        <item>"My Best Exercise Is Something Between A Lunge And A Crunch. It\'s Called Lunch!" </item>
        <item>"Whatever Hurts Most." </item>
        <item>"Whenever I Feel Like Exercise, I Lie Down Until The Feeling Passes." </item>
        <item>"If God Had Wanted Me To Touch My Toes, He Would Have Put Them On My Knees." </item>
        <item>"I Would Do Anything For A Perfect Body, Except Workout." </item>
        <item>"I Don\'t Always Go To The Gym. But When I Do, I Make Sure Everyone On Facebook Knows About It." </item>
        <item>"Dear Santa, Next Christmas All I Want Is A Fat Bank Account, And A Fit Body. Let\'s Try Not To Mix Up The Two Like You Did Last Year Ok?" </item>
        <item>"Sure I Have Rock Hard Abs, I Just Keep Them Under All This Fluff So People Don\'t Like Me Just For My Body!" </item>
        <item>"It Took A Lot Of Will Power, But I Finally Gave Up Dieting" </item>
        <item>"I Did Lose Five Pounds This Week, But Found It In The Refrigerator This Weekend" </item>
        <item>"I\'m Opening A Gym Called "Resolutions." It Will Have Exercise Equipment For The First Two Weeks Of The Year Then Turn Into A Bar For The Rest Of It!" </item>
        <item>"I Believe That Every Human Has A Finite Amount Of Heartbeats. I Don\'t Intend To Waste Any Of Mine Running Around Doing Exercises." </item>
        <item>"I Have To Exercise In The Morning Before My Brain Figures Out What I\'m Doing" </item>
        <item>"I Really Think That Tossing And Turning At Night Should Be Considered Exercise!" </item>
        <item>"Are You Fat And Ugly? Join Our Gym And Just Be Ugly!" </item>
        <item>"I Tried Exercise But Found I Was Allergic To It – My Skin Flushed, My Heart Raced, I Got Sweaty, Short Of Breath. Very Very Dangerous." </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="fitness_author">
        <item>Jack LaLanne </item>
        <item>Joan Welsh </item>
        <item>Henry Ford </item>
        <item>Samuel Johnson </item>
        <item>James Freeman Clarke </item>
        <item>Earl of Derby </item>
        <item>Michael Phelps </item>
        <item>Marcus Tullius Cicero </item>
        <item>Charles Caleb Colton </item>
        <item>Pliny the Younger </item>
        <item>Alex Karras </item>
        <item>Carol Welch </item>
        <item>Elbert Hubbard </item>
        <item>George William Curtis </item>
        <item>Alexander von Humboldt </item>
        <item>Arnold Schwarzenegger </item>
        <item>Julius Erving </item>
        <item>V.L. Allinear </item>
        <item>Virgil </item>
        <item>Elie Wiesel </item>
        <item>Chuang Tzu </item>
        <item>Paul Dudley </item>
        <item>Denis Waitley </item>
        <item>Vince Lombardi </item>
        <item>Bruce Lee </item>
        <item>Thomas Jefferson </item>
        <item>Anthony Robbins </item>
        <item>Lance Armstrong </item>
        <item>Dr. Kenneth Cooper </item>
        <item>T. Campbell and Gisele Lagace </item>
        <item>Chris Adams </item>
        <item>Susie Michelle Cortright </item>
        <item>Sasha Azevedo </item>
        <item>Tiger Woods </item>
        <item>Jack Lalanne </item>
        <item>John F. Kennedy </item>
        <item>Arnold Schwarzenegger </item>
        <item>Ronnie Coleman </item>
        <item>Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson </item>
        <item>Drew Brees </item>
        <item>Mahatma Gandhi </item>
        <item>Ronnie Coleman </item>
        <item>Maurice Green </item>
        <item>Ronnie Coleman </item>
        <item>Muhammad Ali </item>
        <item>Zyzz </item>
        <item>Ryan Lilly </item>
        <item>Greg Everett </item>
        <item>Dan John </item>
        <item>Craig Cecil </item>
        <item>Ernie Taylor </item>
        <item>Conor McGregor </item>
        <item>Jay Cutler </item>
        <item>Arnold Schwarzenegger </item>
        <item>Jack LaLanne </item>
        <item>Les Brown </item>
        <item>Frank Zane </item>
        <item>Phil Heath </item>
        <item>Dorian Yates </item>
        <item>Dwayne The Rock Johnson </item>
        <item>Henry Rollins </item>
        <item>Dwayne The Rock Johnson </item>
        <item>Vince Lombardi </item>
        <item>Arnold Schwarzenegger </item>
        <item>Mike Rashid </item>
        <item>John Romaniello </item>
        <item>Greg Plitt </item>
        <item>Dwayne The Rock Johnson </item>
        <item>Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item>Norman R. Augustine </item>
        <item>Vince Gironda </item>
        <item>Bret Contreras </item>
        <item>Laurence Shahlaei </item>
        <item>Lou Holtz </item>
        <item>William Arthur Ward </item>
        <item>Jess C. Scott </item>
        <item>Bob Harper </item>
        <item>Mark Dilworth </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan </item>
        <item>Justina Chen </item>
        <item>Jack LaLanne </item>
        <item>Tricia Cunningham </item>
        <item>John Bingham </item>
        <item>Dave Tate </item>
        <item>Jack Dempsey </item>
        <item>Ayn Rand </item>
        <item>Auliq Ice </item>
        <item>Bill Loguidice </item>
        <item>Michael Phelps </item>
        <item>Adam Hargreaves </item>
        <item>Edmond Mbiaka </item>
        <item>Mark W. Boyer </item>
        <item>Michael Boyle </item>
        <item>Brooks Kubik </item>
        <item>Mike Tyson </item>
        <item>John Wooden </item>
        <item>Jillian Michaels </item>
        <item>Mark Rippetoe </item>
        <item>Girdhar Joshi </item>
        <item>Pawan Mishra </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>Jillian Michaels </item>
        <item>Noah Galloway </item>
        <item>David Beckham </item>
        <item>Craig Alexander </item>
        <item>Chuck Norris </item>
        <item>L.L. Cool J. </item>
        <item>Ray Lewis </item>
        <item>Drew Brees </item>
        <item>Joe Manganiello </item>
        <item>Cristiano Ronaldo </item>
        <item>Michael Boyle </item>
        <item>Lebron James </item>
        <item>Sylvester Stallone </item>
        <item>Hugh Jackman </item>
        <item>Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson </item>
        <item>  Johnson </item>
        <item>Ronnie Coleman </item>
        <item>Pavel Tsatsouline </item>
        <item>Rich Froning Jr. </item>
        <item>Arnold Schwarzenegger </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Jack Zally </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Dolly Parton </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Neil Armstrong </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>- </item>
        <item>Gym Advertisement Poster </item>
        <item> </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Business Quotes-->
    <string-array name="business_Quotes">
        <item>"The secret of change is to focus all your energy not on fighting the old but on building the new." </item>
        <item>"Always deliver more than expected." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t take too much advice. Most people who have a lot of advice to give — with a few exceptions — generalize whatever they did. Don\'t over-analyze everything." </item>
        <item>"If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader." </item>
        <item>"Every time we launch a feature, people yell at us." </item>
        <item>"Be undeniably good. No marketing effort or social media buzzword can be a substitute for that." </item>
        <item>"What do you need to start a business? Three simple things: know your product better than anyone, know your customer, and have a burning desire to succeed." </item>
        <item>"If you can\'t feed a team with two pizzas, it\'s too large." </item>
        <item>"If people like you, they\'ll listen to you, but if they trust you, they\'ll do business with you." </item>
        <item>"If you are not embarrassed by the first version of your product, you\'ve launched too late." </item>
        <item>"The value of an idea lies in the using of it." </item>
        <item>"The stars will never align, and the traffic lights of life will never all be green at the same time. The universe doesn\'t conspire against you, but it doesn\'t go out of its way to line up the pins either. Conditions are never perfect. ‘Someday\' is a disease that will take your dreams to the grave with you. Pro and con lists are just as bad." </item>
        <item>"Make every detail perfect and limit the number of details to perfect." </item>
        <item>"Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is to love what you do." </item>
        <item>"Always look for the fool in the deal. If you don\'t find one, it\'s you." </item>
        <item>"Your most unhappy customers are your greatest source of learning." </item>
        <item>"If you just work on stuff that you like and you\'re passionate about, you don\'t have to have a master plan with how things will play out." </item>
        <item>"If you define yourself by how you differ from the competition, you\'re probably in trouble." </item>
        <item>"Wonder what your customer really wants? Ask. Don\'t tell." </item>
        <item>"When you find an idea that you just can\'t stop thinking about, that\'s probably a good one to pursue." </item>
        <item>"It\'s not about ideas. It\'s about making ideas happen." </item>
        <item>"Make the most of yourself by fanning the tiny, inner sparks of possibility into flames of achievement." </item>
        <item>"There\'s nothing wrong with staying small. You can do big things with a small team." </item>
        <item>"The fastest way to change yourself is to hang out with people who are already the way you want to be." </item>
        <item>"Chase the vision, not the money, the money will end up following you." </item>
        <item>"The most dangerous poison is the feeling of achievement. The antidote is to every evening think what can be done better tomorrow." </item>
        <item>"Nothing works better than just improving your product." </item>
        <item>"Get five or six of your smartest friends in a room and ask them to rate your idea." </item>
        <item>"Money is like gasoline during a road trip. You don\'t want to run out of gas on your trip, but you\'re not doing a tour of gas stations." </item>
        <item>"Get big quietly, so you don\'t tip off potential competitors." </item>
        <item>"Design is not just what it looks like and feels like. Design is how it works." </item>
        <item>"Character cannot be developed in ease and quiet. Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be strengthened, ambition inspired, and success achieved." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t try to be original, just try to be good." </item>
        <item>"Always think outside the box and embrace opportunities that appear, wherever they might be." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t worry about people stealing your design work. Worry about the day they stop." </item>
        <item>"The last 10% it takes to launch something takes as much energy as the first 90%." </item>
        <item>"If you\'re interested in the living heart of what you do, focus on building things rather than talking about them." </item>
        <item>"Best startups generally come from somebody needing to scratch an itch." </item>
        <item>"Some people dream of success, while other people get up every morning and make it happen." </item>
        <item>"Ideas are easy. Implementation is hard." </item>
        <item>"An entrepreneur is someone who has a vision for something and a want to create." </item>
        <item>"Get a mentor in the applicable field if you\'re at all unsure of what you\'re looking for." </item>
        <item>"Every day that we spent not improving our products was a wasted day." </item>
        <item>"Anything that is measured and watched, improves." </item>
        <item>"Stay self-funded as long as possible." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t play games that you don\'t understand, even if you see lots of other people making money from them." </item>
        <item>"Timing, perseverance, and ten years of trying will eventually make you look like an overnight success." </item>
        <item>"Human beings have an innate inner drive to be autonomous, self-determined and connected to one another. And, when that drive is liberated, people achieve more and live richer lives." </item>
        <item>"Fortunes are built during the down market and collected in the upmarket." </item>
        <item>"It\'s more effective to do something valuable than to hope a logo or name will say it for you." </item>
        <item>"No more romanticizing about how cool it is to be an entrepreneur. It\'s a struggle to save your company\'s life – and your own skin – every day of the week." </item>
        <item>"You can\'t make anything viral, but you can make something good." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t worry about funding if you don\'t need it. Today it\'s cheaper to start a business than ever." </item>
        <item>"Data beats emotions." </item>
        <item>"I never dreamed about success, I worked for it." </item>
        <item>"I try not to make any decisions that I\'m not excited about." </item>
        <item>"See things in the present, even if they are in the future." </item>
        <item>"You don\'t need to have a 100-person company to develop that idea." </item>
        <item>"Ideas are commodity. Execution of them is not." </item>
        <item>"Whether you think you can, or think you can\'t – you\'re right." </item>
        <item>"All humans are entrepreneurs not because they should start companies but because the will to create is encoded in human DNA." </item>
        <item>"The first rule of any technology used in a business is that automation applied to an efficient operation will magnify the efficiency. The second is that automation applied to an inefficient operation will magnify the inefficiency." </item>
        <item>"In the end, a vision without the ability to execute it is probably a hallucination." </item>
        <item>"Step out of the history that is holding you back. Step into the new story you are willing to create." </item>
        <item>"No matter how brilliant your mind or strategy, if you\'re playing a solo game, you\'ll always lose out to a team." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t be cocky. Don\'t be flashy. There\'s always someone better than you." </item>
        <item>"Embrace what you don\'t know, especially in the beginning, because what you don\'t know can become your greatest asset. It ensures that you will absolutely be doing things different from everybody else." </item>
        <item>"Diligence is the mother of good luck." </item>
        <item>"A person who is quietly confident makes the best leader." </item>
        <item>"Risk more than others think is safe. Dream more than others think is practical." </item>
        <item>"Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it." </item>
        <item>"If you can dream it, you can do it." </item>
        <item>"However difficult life may seem, there is always something you can do and succeed at." </item>
        <item>"When I\'m old and dying, I plan to look back on my life and say ‘wow, that was an adventure,\' not ‘wow, I sure felt safe.\'" </item>
        <item>"Accept responsibility for your life. Know that it is you who will get you where you want to go, no one else." </item>
        <item>"The biggest adventure you can take is to live the life of your dreams." </item>
        <item>"You Are Never Too Old To Set Another Goal Or To Dream A New Dream." </item>
        <item>"Live each day as if your life had just begun." </item>
        <item>"Lean forward into your life. Begin each day as if it were on purpose." </item>
        <item>"There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." </item>
        <item>"Do not let the memories of your past limit the potential of your future. There are no limits to what you can achieve on your journey through life, except in your mind." </item>
        <item>"You get in life what you have the courage to ask for." </item>
        <item>"Life isn\'t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself." </item>
        <item>"A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life." </item>
        <item>"Education costs money. But then so does ignorance." </item>
        <item>"The biggest adventure you can take is to live the life of your dreams." </item>
        <item>"Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it." </item>
        <item>"People who succeed have momentum. The more they succeed, the more they want to succeed, and the more they find a way to succeed. Similarly, when someone is failing, the tendency is to get on a downward spiral that can even become a self-fulfilling prophecy." </item>
        <item>"The road to success and the road to failure are almost exactly the same." </item>
        <item>"Would you like me to give you a formula for success? It\'s quite simple, really: Double your rate of failure. You are thinking of failure as the enemy of success. But it isn\'t at all. You can be discouraged by failure or you can learn from it, so go ahead and make mistakes. Make all you can. Because remember that\'s where you will find success." </item>
        <item>"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts." </item>
        <item>"Today\'s Accomplishments Were Yesterday\'s Impossibilities." </item>
        <item>"Success is the sum of small efforts – repeated day in and day out." </item>
        <item>"Successful people do what unsuccessful people are not willing to do. Don\'t wish it were easier; wish you were better." </item>
        <item>"There are no secrets to success. It is the result of preparation, hard work, and learning from failure." </item>
        <item>"A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him." </item>
        <item>"Success seems to be largely a matter of hanging on after others have let go." </item>
        <item>"Try not to become a man of success. Rather become a man of value." </item>
        <item>"Stop chasing the money and start chasing the passion." </item>
        <item>"I never took a day off in my twenties. Not one." </item>
        <item>"I owe my success to having listened respectfully to the very best advice, and then going away and doing the exact opposite." </item>
        <item>"If you really look closely, most overnight successes took a long time." </item>
        <item>"Success seems to be connected with action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes, but they don\'t quit." </item>
        <item>"If you can\'t fly then run. If you can\'t run, then walk. And, if you can\'t walk, then crawl, but whatever you do, you have to keep moving forward." </item>
        <item>"I got lucky because I never gave up the search. Are you quitting too soon? Or, are you willing to pursue luck with a vengeance?" </item>
        <item>"Fall seven times, stand up eight." </item>
        <item>"The real test is not whether you avoid this failure, because you won\'t. It\'s whether you let it harden or shame you into inaction, or whether you learn from it; whether you choose to persevere." </item>
        <item>"Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time." </item>
        <item>"The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty." </item>
        <item>"You have to believe in yourself when no one else does — that makes you a winner right there." </item>
        <item>"We May Encounter Many Defeats But We Must Not Be Defeated." </item>
        <item>"Strength shows not only in the ability to persist, but in the ability to start over." </item>
        <item>"Let me tell you the secret that has led to my goal. My strength lies solely on my tenacity." </item>
        <item>"Never give up on a dream just because of the time it will take to accomplish it. The time will pass anyway." </item>
        <item>"You do what you can for as long as you can, and when you finally can\'t, you do the next best thing. You back up but you don\'t give up." </item>
        <item>"Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better." </item>
        <item>"It\'s fine to celebrate success but it is more important to heed the lessons of failure." </item>
        <item>"So often people are working hard at the wrong thing. Working on the right thing is probably more important than working hard." </item>
        <item>"If you\'re passionate about something and you work hard, then I think you will be successful." </item>
        <item>"I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have." </item>
        <item>"When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better too." </item>
        <item>"A dream does not become reality through magic; it takes sweat, determination and hard work." </item>
        <item>"There is simply no substitute for hard work when it comes to achieving success." </item>
        <item>"Success is no accident. It is hard work, perseverance, learning, studying, sacrifice and most of all, love of what you are doing or learning to do." </item>
        <item>"No great achiever – even those who made it seem easy – ever succeeded without hard work." </item>
        <item>"The only thing that overcomes hard luck is hard work." </item>
        <item>"There is no substitute for hard work." </item>
        <item>"It\'s hard to beat a person who never gives up." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t be afraid to give up the good to go for the great." </item>
        <item>"If you are not willing to risk the usual, you will have to settle for the ordinary." </item>
        <item>"Fearlessness is like a muscle. I know from my own life that the more I exercise it the more natural it becomes to not let my fears run me." </item>
        <item>"You gain strength, courage, and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, I lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along. You must do the thing you think you cannot do." </item>
        <item>"If you can push through that feeling of being scared, that feeling of taking a risk, really amazing things can happen." </item>
        <item>"Believe you can and you\'re halfway there." </item>
        <item>"Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful." </item>
        <item>"Obstacles don\'t have to stop you. If you run into a wall, don\'t turn around and give up. Figure out how to climb it, go through it, or work around it." </item>
        <item>"It always seems impossible until it\'s done." </item>
        <item>"I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions." </item>
        <item>"The Ultimate Measure Of A Man Is Not Where He Stands In Moments Of Comfort And Convenience, But Where He Stands At Times Of Challenge And Controversy." </item>
        <item>"Being Challenged In Life Is Inevitable, Being Defeated Is Optional." </item>
        <item>"Life\'s Challenges Are Not Supposed To Paralyze You, They\'re Supposed To Help You Discover Who You Are." </item>
        <item>"When we least expect it, life sets us a challenge to test our courage and willingness to change; at such a moment, there is no point in pretending that nothing has happened or in saying that we are not yet ready." </item>
        <item>"There are two types of people who will tell you that you cannot make a difference in this world: those who are afraid to try and those who are afraid you will succeed." </item>
        <item>"It is better to fail in originality than to succeed in imitation." </item>
        <item>"Do not be embarrassed by your failures, learn from them and start again." </item>
        <item>"It doesn\'t matter how many times you fail. It doesn\'t matter how many times you almost get it right. No one is going to know or care about your failures, and neither should you." </item>
        <item>"I knew that if I failed I wouldn\'t regret that, but I knew the one thing I might regret is not trying." </item>
        <item>"The only thing worse than starting something and failing… is not starting something." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t worry about failure; you only have to be right once." </item>
        <item>"Failure Will Never Overtake Me If My Determination To Succeed Is Strong Enough." </item>
        <item>"Everything you\'ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t worry about failures, worry about the chances you miss when you don\'t even try." </item>
        <item>"Many of life\'s failures are experienced by people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up." </item>
        <item>"The only real mistake is the one from which we learn nothing." </item>
        <item>"Failure is success if we learn from it." </item>
        <item>"Failure is so important. We speak about success all the time. It is the ability to resist failure or use failure that often leads to greater success. I\'ve met people who don\'t want to try for fear of failing." </item>
        <item>"I\'ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I\'ve lost almost 300 games. Twenty—six times I\'ve been trusted to take the game—winning shot and missed. I\'ve failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed." </item>
        <item>"People often say that motivation doesn\'t last. Well, neither does bathing – that\'s why we recommend it daily." </item>
        <item>"I always wanted to be somebody, but now I realise I should have been more specific." </item>
        <item>"The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking spaces." </item>
        <item>"I didn\'t fail the test. I just found 100 ways to do it wrong." </item>
        <item>"When I hear somebody sigh, Life is hard, I am always tempted to ask, ‘Compared to what?\'" </item>
        <item>"The elevator to success is out of order. You\'ll have to use the stairs… one step at a time." </item>
        <item>"Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work." </item>
        <item>"You must learn from the mistakes of others. You can\'t possibly live long enough to make them all yourself." </item>
        <item>"Listen, smile, agree, and then do whatever you were gonna do anyway." </item>
        <item>"Remember, today is the tomorrow you worried about yesterday." </item>
        <item>"Even if you are on the right track, you\'ll get run over if you just sit there." </item>
        <item>"Nobody is gonna hit as hard as life, but it ain\'t how hard you can hit. It\'s how hard you can get hit and keep moving forward. It\'s how much you can take, and keep moving forward. That\'s how winning is done." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t ever let somebody tell you you can\'t do something, not even me. Alright? You dream, you gotta protect it. People can\'t do something themselves, they wanna tell you you can\'t do it. If you want something, go get it. Period." </item>
        <item>"The only thing standing between you and your goal is the bullshit story you keep telling yourself as to why you can\'t achieve it." </item>
        <item>"All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to us." </item>
        <item>"Great men are not born great, they grow great." </item>
        <item>"Some people can\'t believe in themselves until someone else believes in them first." </item>
        <item>"Why do we fall sir? So that we can learn to pick ourselves up." </item>
        <item>"Life moves pretty fast. If you don\'t stop and look around once in a while, you could miss it." </item>
        <item>"After a while, you learn to ignore the names people call you and just trust who you are." </item>
        <item>"Our lives are defined by opportunities, even the ones we miss." </item>
        <item>"What we do in life echoes in eternity." </item>
        <item>"Sometimes it is the people who no one imagines anything of who do the things that no one can imagine." </item>
        <item>"Every man dies, but not every man really lives." </item>
        <item>"Someone I once knew wrote that we walk away from our dreams afraid that we may fail or worse yet, afraid we may succeed." </item>
        <item>"It is not our abilities that show what we truly are. It is our choices." </item>
        <item>"There should be no boundaries to human endeavor. We are all different. However bad life may seem, there is always something you can do, and succeed at. While there\'s life, there is hope." </item>
        <item>"The accident is your training. Life is a choice. You can choose to be a victim or anything else you\'d like to be." </item>
        <item>"In this lifetime, you don\'t have to prove nothing to nobody, except yourself. And after what you\'ve gone through, if you haven\'t done that by now, it ain\'t gonna never happen." </item>
        <item>"It\'s supposed to be hard. If it wasn\'t hard, everyone would do it. The hard is what makes it great." </item>
        <item>"Oh yes, the past can hurt. But you can either run from it, or learn from it." </item>
        <item>"No matter what anybody tells you, words and ideas can change the world." </item>
        <item>"You mustn\'t be afraid to dream a little bigger, darling." </item>
        <item>"Find a truly original idea. It is the only way I will ever distinguish myself. It is the only way I will ever matter." </item>
        <item>"If you are working on something that you really care about, you don\'t have to be pushed. The vision pulls you." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t say you don\'t have enough time. You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were given to Helen Keller, Pasteur, Michelangelo, Mother Teresa, Leonardo Da Vinci, Thomas Jefferson, and Albert Einstein." </item>
        <item>"The more I want to get something done the less I call it work." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t count the days, make the days count." </item>
        <item>"A year from now you may wish you had started today." </item>
        <item>"Someday is not a day of the week." </item>
        <item>"What we fear of doing most is usually what we most need to do." </item>
        <item>"Make each day your masterpiece." </item>
        <item>"Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work." </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="business_authotr">
        <item>Socrates, father of Western philosophy  </item>
        <item>Larry Page, co-founder of Google  </item>
        <item>Ben Silbermann, founder of Pinterest  </item>
        <item>John Quincy Adams, 6th President of the United States  </item>
        <item>Angelo Sotira, co-founder of deviantART  </item>
        <item>Anthony Volodkin, founder of Hype Machine  </item>
        <item>Dave Thomas, Founder of Wendy\'s  </item>
        <item>Jeff Bezos, Founder and CEO of Amazon  </item>
        <item>Zig Ziglar, author, salesman, and motivational speaker  </item>
        <item>Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn  </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison, co-founder of General Electric  </item>
        <item>Tim Ferriss  </item>
        <item>Jack Dorsey, co-founder of Twitter  </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs, co-founder, Chairman and CEO of Apple Inc.  </item>
        <item>Mark Cuban, AXS TV Chairman and entrepreneur  </item>
        <item>Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft  </item>
        <item>Mark Zuckerberg, founder of Facebook  </item>
        <item>Omar Hamoui, co-founder of AdMob  </item>
        <item>Lisa Stone, co-founder and CEO of BlogHer  </item>
        <item>Josh James, CEO and co-founder of Omniture  </item>
        <item>Scott Belsky, co-founder of Behance  </item>
        <item>Golda Meir, fourth Prime Minister of Israel  </item>
        <item>Jason Fried, 37signals founder and co-author of Rework  </item>
        <item>Reid Hoffman, LinkedIn co-founder  </item>
        <item>Tony Hsieh, CEO of Zappos  </item>
        <item>Ingvar Kamprad, founder of IKEA  </item>
        <item>Joel Spolsky, co-founder of Stack Overflow  </item>
        <item>Mark Pincus, CEO of Zynga  </item>
        <item>Tim O\'Reilly, founder, and CEO of O\'Reilly Media  </item>
        <item>Chris Dixon, an investor at Andreessen Horowitz  </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs, co-founder, Chairman, and CEO of Apple Inc.  </item>
        <item>Helen Keller, American author, political activist and lecturer  </item>
        <item>Paul Rand, Graphic Designer  </item>
        <item>Lakshmi Mittal, Chairman &amp; CEO of ArcelorMittal  </item>
        <item>Jeffrey Zeldman, entrepreneur and web designer  </item>
        <item>Rob Kalin, founder of Etsy  </item>
        <item>Ryan Freitas, co-founder of About.me  </item>
        <item>Michael Arrington, founder and co-editor of TechCrunch  </item>
        <item>Wayne Huizenga, prolific American business person, owner of Blockbuster Video and the Miami Dolphins.  </item>
        <item>Guy Kawasaki, entrepreneur and co-founder of Alltop  </item>
        <item>David Karp, founder, and CEO of Tumblr  </item>
        <item>Kyle Bragger, founder of Forrst, and co-founder of Exposure  </item>
        <item>Joel Spolsky, co-founder of Stack Overflow  </item>
        <item>Bob Parsons, founder of GoDaddy  </item>
        <item>Garrett Camp, founder of Expa, Uber, and StumbleUpon  </item>
        <item>Tony Hsieh, CEO of Zappos  </item>
        <item>Biz Stone, co-founder of Twitter  </item>
        <item>Daniel Pink, author  </item>
        <item>Jason Calacanis, founder of LAUNCH Ticker  </item>
        <item>Jason Cohen, founder of Smartbear Software  </item>
        <item>Spencer Fry, co-founder of CarbonMade  </item>
        <item>Peter Shankman, founder of HARO  </item>
        <item>Noah Everett, founder of Twitpic  </item>
        <item>Sean Rad, founder of Tinder  </item>
        <item>Estee Lauder, founder of Estee Lauder Cosmetics  </item>
        <item>Jake Nickell, founder and CEO of Threadless  </item>
        <item>Larry Ellison, co-founder of Oracle  </item>
        <item>Larry Page, co-founder of Google  </item>
        <item>Michael Dell, chairman, and CEO of Dell  </item>
        <item>Henry Ford, founder of the Ford Motor Company  </item>
        <item>Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn </item>
        <item>Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft  </item>
        <item>Steve Case, co-founder of AOL  </item>
        <item>Oprah Winfrey, media proprietor  </item>
        <item>Reid Hoffman, LinkedIn co-founder  </item>
        <item>Tony Hsieh, CEO of Zappos  </item>
        <item>Sara Blakely, founder of SPANX  </item>
        <item>Benjamin Franklin, a Founding Father of the United States  </item>
        <item>Fred Wilson, co-founder of Union Square Ventures  </item>
        <item>Howard Schultz, CEO of Starbucks  </item>
        <item>Charles R. Swindoll, author, educator, and radio preacher </item>
        <item>Walt Disney, founder of the Disney Brother Studio and Disneyland </item>
        <item>Stephen Hawking, English theoretical physicist, cosmologist, and author </item>
        <item>Tom Preston-Werner, co-founder of Github </item>
        <item>Les Brown, American motivational speaker, author, and former politician </item>
        <item>Oprah Winfrey, media proprietor </item>
        <item>C.S. Lewis, British writer </item>
        <item>Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe, German writer </item>
        <item>Mary Anne Radmacher, author </item>
        <item>Maya Angelou, American poet, singer, and civil rights activist </item>
        <item>Roy T. Bennett, author </item>
        <item>Oprah Winfrey, media proprietor </item>
        <item>George Bernard Shaw, Irish playwright </item>
        <item>Charles Darwin, English naturalist, geologist and biologist </item>
        <item>Sir Claus Moser, British statistician </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan, American former professional basketball player </item>
        <item>Henry David Thoreau, essayist, poet, and philosopher </item>
        <item>Tony Robbins, life and business strategist, and author </item>
        <item>Colin R. Davis, English conductor for the London Symphony Orchestra </item>
        <item>Thomas J. Watson </item>
        <item>Winston Churchill, Prime Minister of Great Britain during World War II </item>
        <item>Robert H. Schuller, American motivational speaker </item>
        <item>Robert Collier, author </item>
        <item>Jim Rohn, one of America\'s foremost business philosophers </item>
        <item>Colin Powell, US statesman and retired four-star General in the United States Army </item>
        <item>David Brinkley, newscaster for NBC and ABC </item>
        <item>William Feather, American publisher and author </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein, theoretical physicist </item>
        <item>Tony Hsieh, CEO of Zappos </item>
        <item>Bill Gates, Microsoft co-founder </item>
        <item>G. K. Chesterton, English writer, poet, and philosopher </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs, co-founder, Chairman and CEO of Apple Inc. </item>
        <item>Conrad Hilton, Founder of the Hilton Hotels chain </item>
        <item>Martin Luther King Jr., leader of the civil rights movement </item>
        <item>Jill Konrath, speaker, author and thought leader </item>
        <item>Japanese Proverb </item>
        <item>Barack Obama, 44th President of the United States </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison, entrepreneur and inventor </item>
        <item> Winston Churchill, Prime Minister of Great Britain during World War II </item>
        <item>Venus Williams, American professional tennis player </item>
        <item>Maya Angelou, American poet, singer, and civil rights activist </item>
        <item>F. Scott Fitzgerald, American fiction writer </item>
        <item>Louis Pasteur, French biologist, microbiologist and chemist </item>
        <item>Earl Nightingale, American radio speaker and author </item>
        <item>Chuck Yeager, former United States Air Force officer </item>
        <item>Samuel Beckett, Irish avant-garde novelist and playwright </item>
        <item>Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft </item>
        <item>Caterina Fake, Flickr co-founder </item>
        <item>Pierre Omidyar, founder and chairman of Ebay </item>
        <item>Thomas Jefferson, Founding Father and President of the United States </item>
        <item>Paulo Coelho,  Brazilian lyricist and novelist </item>
        <item>Colin Powell, US statesman and retired four-star General in the United States Army </item>
        <item>Heather Bresch, CEO of Mylan </item>
        <item>Pele, Brazilian retired professional footballer </item>
        <item>Jonathan Sacks, British author and politician </item>
        <item>Harry Golden, American writer </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison, entrepreneur and inventor </item>
        <item>Babe Ruth, American professional baseball player </item>
        <item>John D. Rockefeller,  American oil industry business magnate </item>
        <item>Jim Rohn, American entrepreneur, author and motivational speaker </item>
        <item>Arianna Huffington, president of The Huffington Post Media Group </item>
        <item>Eleanor Roosevelt, known as "First Lady of the World" for her human rights advocacy </item>
        <item>Marissa Mayer, president &amp; CEO of Yahoo! </item>
        <item>Theodore Roosevelt, 26th President of the United States </item>
        <item>Joshua J. Marine, author </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan, former professional basketball player </item>
        <item>Nelson Mandela, Former President of South Africa, political leader, and philanthropist </item>
        <item>Stephen Covey, American educator, author, and businessman </item>
        <item>Martin Luther King, Jr., leader of the civil rights movement </item>
        <item>Roger Crawford, public speaker, author, and certified tennis professional </item>
        <item>Bernice Johnson Reagon, song leader, composer, and social activist </item>
        <item>Paulo Coelho </item>
        <item>Ray Goforth, director of strategy and partnerships at Spredfast </item>
        <item>Herman Melville, American novelist </item>
        <item>Richard Branson, founder of the Virgin Group </item>
        <item>Mark Cuban, entrepreneur, owner of Landmark Theaters and Chairman of AXS TV </item>
        <item>Jeff Bezos, founder, and CEO of Amazon </item>
        <item>Seth Godin, author, entrepreneur, and blogger </item>
        <item>Drew Houston, founder and CEO of Dropbox </item>
        <item>Og Mandino, American author </item>
        <item>George Addair, real-estate developer </item>
        <item>Jack Canfield, American author, motivational speaker, corporate trainer, and entrepreneur </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison, entrepreneur and inventor </item>
        <item>Henry Ford, founder of the Ford Motor Company </item>
        <item>Malcolm Forbes, American entrepreneur and publisher of Forbes magazine </item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling, British novelist </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan, former professional basketball player </item>
        <item>Zig Ziglar, American author </item>
        <item>Lily Tomlin, American actress </item>
        <item> Will Rogers, American actor </item>
        <item>Benjamin Franklin, Founding Father of the United States </item>
        <item>Sydney Harris, American journalist </item>
        <item>Joe Girard, American salesman </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison, entrepreneur and inventor </item>
        <item>Sam Levenson, American humorist </item>
        <item>Robert Downey Jr., American actor </item>
        <item>Dale Carnegie, American writer </item>
        <item>Will Rogers, American actor </item>
        <item>Rocky, Rocky Balboa </item>
        <item>Chris Gardner, The Pursuit of Happyness </item>
        <item>Jordan Belfort, Wolf of the Wall Street </item>
        <item>Gandalf, Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring </item>
        <item>Vito Corleone, The Godfather </item>
        <item>Sean Maguire, Good Will Hunting </item>
        <item>Alfred, Batman Begins </item>
        <item>Ferris, Ferris Bueller\'s Day Off </item>
        <item>Shrek, Shrek The Third </item>
        <item>Benjamin Button, The Curious Case of Benjamin Button </item>
        <item>Maximus, from Gladiator </item>
        <item>Alan Turing, The Imitation Game </item>
        <item>William Wallace, Braveheart </item>
        <item>Forrester, Finding Forrester </item>
        <item>Dumbledore, Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets </item>
        <item>Stephen Hawking, The Theory of Everything </item>
        <item>Socrates, from Peaceful Warrior </item>
        <item>Fortune, Rudy </item>
        <item>Jimmy Dugan, A League of Their Own </item>
        <item>Rafiki, The Lion King </item>
        <item>John Keating, Dead Poets Society </item>
        <item>Eames, Inception </item>
        <item>John Nash, A Beautiful Mind </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs, co-founder, Chairman and CEO of Apple Inc. </item>
        <item>H. Jackson Brown Jr., American author </item>
        <item>Richard Bach, American writer </item>
        <item>Muhammad Ali, American professional boxer </item>
        <item>Karen Lamb, author </item>
        <item>Janet Dailey, author </item>
        <item>Ralph Waldo Emerson, essayist, philosopher, and poet </item>
        <item>John Wooden, American basketball player </item>
        <item>Aristotle, father of Western philosophy </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--General Quotes-->
    <string-array name="general_Quotes">
        <item>Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever. </item>
        <item>That which does not kill us makes us stronger. </item>
        <item>Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don\'t matter and those who matter don\'t mind. </item>
        <item>We must not allow other people\'s limited perceptions to define us. </item>
        <item>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken. </item>
        <item>This above all: to thine own self be true. </item>
        <item>If opportunity doesn\'t knock, build a door. </item>
        <item>Wise men speak because they have something to say; fools because they have to say something. </item>
        <item>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value. </item>
        <item>Two roads diverged in a wood, and I-I took the one less traveled by, And that has made all the difference. </item>
        <item>Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. </item>
        <item>Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect. </item>
        <item>I haven\'t failed. I\'ve just found 10,000 ways that won\'t work. </item>
        <item>A journey of a thousand leagues begins beneath one\'s feet. </item>
        <item>I\'ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel. </item>
        <item>Either you run the day, or the day runs you. </item>
        <item>Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one\'s courage. </item>
        <item>You must be the change you wish to see in the world. </item>
        <item>What you do speaks so loudly that I cannot hear what you say. </item>
        <item>Believe and act as if it were impossible to fail. </item>
        <item>The difference between ordinary and extraordinary is that little extra. </item>
        <item>The best way to predict the future is to invent it. </item>
        <item>If I am not for myself, who is for me? And if I am only for myself, what am I? And if not now, when? </item>
        <item>"Everything has beauty, but not everyone can see." </item>
        <item>Believe you can and you\'re halfway there. </item>
        <item>How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world. </item>
        <item>Imagination is everything. It is the preview of life\'s coming attractions. </item>
        <item>Change your thoughts and you change your world. </item>
        <item>Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions. </item>
        <item>Remember that happiness is a way of travel, not a destination. </item>
        <item>Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears. </item>
        <item>If you want to lift yourself up, lift up someone else. </item>
        <item>You miss 100% of the shots you don\'t take. </item>
        <item>It is never too late to be what you might have been. </item>
        <item>A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new. </item>
        <item>The person who says it cannot be done should not interrupt the person who is doing it. </item>
        <item>Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds discuss people. </item>
        <item>You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough. </item>
        <item>If you tell the truth, you don\'t have to remember anything. </item>
        <item>The only thing worse than being blind is having sight but no vision. </item>
        <item>To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all. </item>
        <item>Darkness cannot drive out darkness; only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate; only love can do that. </item>
        <item>The only thing we have to fear is fear itself. </item>
        <item>If you look at what you have in life, you\'ll always have more. If you look at what you don\'t have in life, you\'ll never have enough. </item>
        <item>Remember no one can make you feel inferior without your consent. </item>
        <item>For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness. </item>
        <item>Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage. </item>
        <item>There are two ways of spreading light: to be the candle or the mirror that reflects it. </item>
        <item>The road to success and the road to failure are almost exactly the same. </item>
        <item>Motivation is a fire from within. If someone else tries to light that fire under you, chances are it will burn very briefly. </item>
        <item>In three words I can sum up everything I\'ve learned about life: It goes on. </item>
        <item>Self-reverence, self-knowledge, self control - these three alone lead to power. </item>
        <item>Though no one can go back and make a brand new start, anyone can start from now and make a brand new ending. </item>
        <item>Anyone who stops learning is old, whether at twenty or eighty. Anyone who keeps learning stays young. The greatest thing in life is to keep your mind young. </item>
        <item>He who angers you conquers you. </item>
        <item>Beauty, without expression, tires. </item>
        <item>The secret of business is to know something that nobody else knows. </item>
        <item>The greatest discovery of all time is that a person can change his future by merely changing his attitude. </item>
        <item>We cannot always build the future of our youth, but we can build our youth for the future. </item>
        <item>It takes courage to grow up and turn out to be who you really are. </item>
        <item>In this world nothing can be said to be certain, except death and taxes. </item>
        <item>It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. </item>
        <item>A happy family is but an earlier heaven. </item>
        <item>Don\'t walk in front of me, I may not follow. Don\'t walk behind me, I may not lead. Walk beside me and be my friend. </item>
        <item>Courage doesn\'t always roar. Sometimes courage is the little voice at the end of the day that says \'I\'ll try again tomorrow.\' </item>
        <item>Education is like a double-edged sword. It may be turned to dangerous uses if it is not properly handled. </item>
        <item>Walking with a friend in the dark is better than walking alone in the light. </item>
        <item>Happiness is not a goal; it is a by-product. </item>
        <item>Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much. </item>
        <item>The only true wisdom is knowing that you know nothing. </item>
        <item>As a well-spent day brings happy sleep, so a life well spent brings happy death. </item>
        <item>Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak. Courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen. </item>
        <item>Children are our most valuable resource. </item>
        <item>Love is, above all else, the gift of oneself. </item>
        <item>Music in the soul can be heard by the universe. </item>
        <item>Peace begins with a smile. </item>
        <item>Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it. </item>
        <item>A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you. </item>
        <item>Never leave that till tomorrow which you can do today. </item>
        <item>If you don\'t make mistakes, you\'re not working on hard enough problems. </item>
        <item>We must learn to live together as brothers or perish together as fools. </item>
        <item>Life is like a camera. Just focus on what\'s important, capture the good times, develop from the negatives, and if things don\'t work out, just take another shot. </item>
        <item>When you judge another, you do not define them; you define yourself. </item>
        <item>Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work. </item>
        <item>Love me when I least deserve it, because that\'s when I really need it. </item>
        <item>The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen or even touched. They must be felt with the heart. </item>
        <item>If you want to test your memory, try to recall what you were worrying about one year ago today. </item>
        <item>The real opportunity for success lies within the person and not in the job. </item>
        <item>It takes a great deal of courage to stand up to your enemies, but even more to stand up to your friends. </item>
        <item>Defeat is not bitter unless you swallow it. </item>
        <item>"A mind is like a parachute. It doesn\'t work if it isn\'t open." </item>
        <item>The man who removes a mountain begins by carrying away small stones. </item>
        <item>When you are totally at peace with yourself, nothing can shake you. </item>
        <item>Be a first rate version of yourself, not a second rate version of someone else. </item>
        <item>Your worth consists in what you are and not in what you have. </item>
        <item>Others can stop you temporarily - you are the only one who can do it permanently. </item>
        <item>Life has no limitations, except the ones you make. </item>
        <item>Peace comes from within. Do not seek it without. </item>
        <item>How many cares one loses when one decides not to be something but to be someone. </item>
        <item>Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don\'t matter and those who matter don\'t mind. </item>
        <item>Imitation is suicide. </item>
        <item>Do your own thing on your own terms and get what you came here for. </item>
        <item>Flatter yourself critically. </item>
        <item>Do what you feel in your heart to be right, for you\'ll be criticized anyway. </item>
        <item>Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect. </item>
        <item>I will not let anyone walk through my mind with their dirty feet. </item>
        <item>Better to write for yourself and have no public, than to write for the public and have no self. </item>
        <item>We must not allow other people\'s limited perceptions to define us. </item>
        <item>Don\'t look for society to give you permission to be yourself. </item>
        <item>If things go wrong, don\'t go with them. </item>
        <item>Wanting to be someone else is a waste of who you are. </item>
        <item>Tension is who you think you should be. Relaxation is who you are. </item>
        <item>Where\'s your will to be weird? </item>
        <item>Some people say you are going the wrong way, when it\'s simply a way of your own. </item>
        <item>Remember to always be yourself. Unless you suck. </item>
        <item>Do what you can, with what you have, where you are. </item>
        <item>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken. </item>
        <item>I took a deep breath and listened to the old bray of my heart. I am. I am. I am. </item>
        <item>There came a time when the risk to remain tight in the bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom. </item>
        <item>To find yourself, think for yourself. </item>
        <item>If you seek authenticity for authenticity\'s sake you are no longer authentic. </item>
        <item>If you cannot be a poet, be the poem. </item>
        <item>When one is pretending the entire body revolts. </item>
        <item>Be there for others, but never leave yourself behind. </item>
        <item>Do what you must, And your friends will adjust. </item>
        <item>Just let awareness have its way with you completely. </item>
        <item>We must be our own before we can be another\'s. </item>
        <item>This above all: to thine own self be true. </item>
        <item>Get busy living or get busy dying. </item>
        <item>The first step toward success is taken when you refuse to be a captive of the environment in which you first find yourself. </item>
        <item>When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us. </item>
        <item>Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn\'t do than by the ones you did do. </item>
        <item>When I dare to be powerful - to use my strength in the service of my vision, then it becomes less and less important whether I am afraid. </item>
        <item>A friend is one that knows you as you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow. </item>
        <item>Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds discuss people. </item>
        <item>A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him. </item>
        <item>Those who dare to fail miserably can achieve greatly. </item>
        <item>I can\'t give you a sure-fire formula for success, but I can give you a formula for failure: try to please everybody all the time. </item>
        <item>You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough.  </item>
        <item>Double your rate of failure. You are thinking of failure as the enemy of success. But it isn\'t at all. You can be discouraged by failure or you can learn from it, so go ahead and make mistakes. Make all you can. Because remember that\'s where you will find success. </item>
        <item>He that falls in love with himself will have no rivals.  </item>
        <item>It is hard to fail, but it is worse never to have tried to succeed. </item>
        <item>I\'m a success today because I had a friend who believed in me and I didn\'t have the heart to let him down. </item>
        <item>Love yourself first and everything else falls into line. You really have to love yourself to get anything done in this world. </item>
        <item>Let us always meet each other with smile, for the smile is the beginning of love. </item>
        <item>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful. </item>
        <item>When one door closes, another opens; but we often look so long and so regretfully upon the closed door that we do not see the one that has opened for us. </item>
        <item>Our greatest fear should not be of failure… but of succeeding at things in life that don\'t really matter. </item>
        <item>It had long since come to my attention that people of accomplishment rarely sat back and let things happen to them. They went out and happened to things. </item>
        <item>Remember that the happiest people are not those getting more, but those giving more. </item>
        <item>The only impossible journey is the one you never begin.  </item>
        <item>It is our choices, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities. </item>
        <item>Only put off until tomorrow what you are willing to die having left undone. </item>
        <item>If you want to be happy, be. </item>
        <item>Many of life\'s failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up. </item>
        <item>If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal, not to people or things. </item>
        <item>Success is just a war of attrition. Sure, there\'s an element of talent you should probably possess. But if you just stick around long enough, eventually something is going to happen. </item>
        <item>The opposite of love is not hate; it\'s indifference. </item>
        <item>Life is ten percent what happens to you and ninety percent how you respond to it.  </item>
        <item>The good news is that the moment you decide that what you know is more important than what you have been taught to believe, you will have shifted gears in your quest for abundance. Success comes from within, not from without. </item>
        <item>I never knew how to worship until I knew how to love. </item>
        <item>Every great dream begins with a dreamer. Always remember, you have within you the strength, the patience, and the passion to reach for the stars to change the world. </item>
        <item>It is impossible to escape the impression that people commonly use false standards of measurement - that they seek power, success and wealth for themselves and admire them in others, and that they underestimate what is of true value in life. </item>
        <item>A friend is someone who gives you total freedom to be yourself. </item>
        <item>All that we see and seem is but a dream within a dream.  </item>
        <item>Every great dream begins with a dreamer. Always remember, you have within you the strength, the patience, and the passion to reach for the stars to change the world. </item>
        <item>Never let the fear of striking out keep you from playing the game. </item>
        <item>Live in the sunshine, swim the sea, drink the wild air. </item>
        <item>Life is trying things to see if they work. </item>
        <item>Success in business requires training and discipline and hard work. But if you\'re not frightened by these things, the opportunities are just as great today as they ever were. </item>
        <item>The purpose of our lives is to be happy.  </item>
        <item>The No. 1 reason people fail in life is because they listen to their friends, family, and neighbors. </item>
        <item>Your time is limited, so don\'t waste it living someone else\'s life. Don\'t be trapped by dogma - which is living with the results of other people\'s thinking. </item>
        <item>Success is how high you bounce when you hit bottom. </item>
        <item>You will face many defeats in life, but never let yourself be defeated. </item>
        <item>May you live all the days of your life. </item>
        <item>In three words I can sum up everything I\'ve learned about life: It goes on. </item>
        <item>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts. </item>
        <item>You\'re not obligated to win. You\'re obligated to keep trying. To the best you can do everyday. </item>
        <item>If life were predictable it would cease to be life, and be without flavor. </item>
        <item>If you don\'t design your own life plan, chances are you\'ll fall into someone else\'s plan. And guess what they have planned for you? Not much. </item>
        <item>The question isn\'t who is going to let me; it\'s who is going to stop me. </item>
        <item>Life is like a box of chocolates. You never know what you\'re going to get.  </item>
        <item>The three great essentials to achieve anything worthwhile are, first, hard work; second, stick-to-itiveness; third, common sense. </item>
        <item>The successful warrior is the average man, with laser-like focus. </item>
        <item>A man is a success if he gets up in the morning and gets to bed at night, and in between he does what he wants to do. </item>
        <item>Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, today is a gift of God, which is why we call it the present. </item>
        <item>Life isn\'t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself. </item>
        <item>The whole secret of a successful life is to find out what is one\'s destiny to do, and then do it. </item>
        <item>Success? I don\'t know what that word means. I\'m happy. But success, that goes back to what in somebody\'s eyes success means. For me, success is inner peace. That\'s a good day for me. </item>
        <item>A kiss is a lovely trick designed by nature to stop speech when words become superfluous. </item>
        <item>You miss 100 percent of the shots you never take. </item>
        <item>Life itself is the most wonderful fairy tale.  </item>
        <item>In order to write about life first you must live it. </item>
        <item>Do not go where the path may lead; go instead where there is no path and leave a trail. </item>
        <item>We are what we repeatedly do; excellence, then, is not an act but a habit. </item>
        <item>Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much. </item>
        <item>The big lesson in life, baby, is never be scared of anyone or anything. </item>
        <item>If you aren\'t going all the way, why go at all?  </item>
        <item>To love and be loved is to feel the sun from both sides. </item>
        <item>Love is an irresistible desire to be irresistibly desired. </item>
        <item>Those who believe in telekinetics, raise my hand. </item>
        <item>I only regret that I have but one life to give for my country. </item>
        <item>The person who reads too much and uses his brain too little will fall into lazy habits of thinking. </item>
        <item>Life would be tragic if it weren\'t funny.  </item>
        <item>Better to have loved and lost, than to have never loved at all. </item>
        <item>Every child is an artist, the problem is staying an artist when you grow up. </item>
        <item>Have no fear of perfection, you\'ll never reach it. </item>
        <item>Life is not a problem to be solved, but a reality to be experienced. </item>
        <item>Curiosity about life in all of its aspects, I think, is still the secret of great creative people. </item>
        <item>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken.  </item>
        <item>Imagination is the beginning of creation. You imagine what you desire, you will what you imagine, and at last, you create what you will. </item>
        <item>The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step. </item>
        <item>Imagination was given to man to compensate him for what he is not, and a sense of humor was provided to console him for what he is. </item>
        <item>What you do speaks so loudly that I cannot hear what you say. </item>
        <item>Be the living expression of God\'s kindness; kindness in your face, kindness in your eyes, kindness in your smile, kindness in your warm greeting. </item>
        <item>Be happy for this moment. This moment is your life.  </item>
        <item>You must be the change you wish to see in the world. </item>
        <item>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value. </item>
        <item>Keep your face to the sunshine and you can never see the shadow. </item>
        <item>The best way out is always through. </item>
        <item>The dream crossed twilight between birth and dying. </item>
        <item>People are just as happy as they make up their minds to be.  </item>
        <item>Don\'t think. Thinking is the enemy of creativity. It\'s self-conscious, and anything self-conscious is lousy. You can\'t try to do things. You simply must do things. </item>
        <item>Creativity is just connecting things. When you ask creative people how they did something, they feel a little guilty because they didn\'t really do it, the just saw something. It seemed obvious to them after a while. </item>
        <item>Sing like no one\'s listening, love like you\'ve never been hurt, dance like nobody\'s watching, and live like it\'s heaven on earth. </item>
        <item>The power of imagination makes us infinite. </item>
        <item>Doing the best at this moment puts you in the best place for the next moment. </item>
        <item>Originality is nothing but judicious imitation. </item>
        <item>Life is made of ever so many partings welded together. </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="general_authotr">
        <item> Mahatma Gandhi </item>
        <item> Friedrich Nietzsche </item>
        <item> Bernard M. Baruch </item>
        <item> Virginia Satir </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> William Shakespeare </item>
        <item> Milton Berle </item>
        <item> Plato </item>
        <item> Albert Einstein </item>
        <item> Robert Frost </item>
        <item> John Wooden </item>
        <item> Mark Twain </item>
        <item> Thomas Edison </item>
        <item> Lao Tzu </item>
        <item> Maya Angelou </item>
        <item> Jim Rohn </item>
        <item> Anais Nin </item>
        <item> Mahatma Gandhi </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Charles Kettering </item>
        <item> Jimmy Johnson </item>
        <item> Alan Kay </item>
        <item> Rabbi Hillel </item>
        <item> Confucius </item>
        <item> Theodore Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Anne Frank </item>
        <item> Albert Einstein </item>
        <item> Norman Vincent </item>
        <item> Dalai Lama </item>
        <item> Roy M. Goodman </item>
        <item> Les Brown </item>
        <item> Booker T. Washington </item>
        <item> Wayne Gretzky </item>
        <item> George Eliot </item>
        <item> Albert Einstein </item>
        <item> Chinese Proverb </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Mae West </item>
        <item> Mark Twain </item>
        <item> Helen Keller </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> Martin Luther King, Jr. </item>
        <item> Franklin D. Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Oprah Winfrey </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Lao Tzu </item>
        <item> Edith Wharton </item>
        <item> Colin R. Davis </item>
        <item> Stephen R. Covey </item>
        <item> Robert Frost </item>
        <item> Alfred, Lord Tennyson </item>
        <item> Carl Bard </item>
        <item> Henry Ford </item>
        <item> Elizabeth Kenny </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Aristotle Onassis </item>
        <item> Oprah Winfrey </item>
        <item> Franklin D. Roosevelt </item>
        <item> E.E. Cummings </item>
        <item> Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item> Aristotle </item>
        <item> George Bernard Shaw </item>
        <item> Albert Camus </item>
        <item> Mary Anne Radmacher </item>
        <item> Wu Ting-Fang </item>
        <item> Helen Keller </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> Socrates </item>
        <item> Leonardo da Vinci </item>
        <item> Winston Churchill </item>
        <item> Herbert Hoover </item>
        <item> Jean Anouilh </item>
        <item> Lao Tzu </item>
        <item> Mother Teresa </item>
        <item> Maya Angelou </item>
        <item> Elbert Hubbard </item>
        <item> Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item> Frank Wilczek </item>
        <item> Martin Luther King, Jr. </item>
        <item> Unknown </item>
        <item> Wayne Dyer </item>
        <item> Thomas Edison </item>
        <item> Swedish Proverb </item>
        <item> Helen Keller </item>
        <item> E. Joseph Cossman </item>
        <item> Zig Ziglar </item>
        <item> J. K. Rowling </item>
        <item> Joe Clark </item>
        <item> Frank Zappa </item>
        <item> Chinese Proverbs </item>
        <item> Deepam Chatterjee </item>
        <item> Judy Garland </item>
        <item> Thomas Edison </item>
        <item> Zig Ziglar </item>
        <item> Les Brown </item>
        <item> Buddha </item>
        <item> -Gabrielle "Coco" Chanel </item>
        <item> Dr. Seuss </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Oliver James </item>
        <item> Willis Goth Regier </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Mark Twain </item>
        <item> Mahatma Gandhi </item>
        <item> Cyril Connolly </item>
        <item> Virginia Satir </item>
        <item> Steve Maraboli </item>
        <item> Roger Babson </item>
        <item> Kurt Cobain </item>
        <item> Chinese Proverb </item>
        <item> Jim Morrison </item>
        <item> Angelina Jolie </item>
        <item> Joss Whedon </item>
        <item> Theodore Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> Sylvia Plath </item>
        <item> Anaïs Nin </item>
        <item> Socrates </item>
        <item> Jean Paul Sartre </item>
        <item> David Carradine </item>
        <item> Anaïs Nin </item>
        <item> Dodinsky </item>
        <item> Robert Brault </item>
        <item> Scott Morrison </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> William Shakespeare </item>
        <item> Stephen King </item>
        <item> Mark Caine </item>
        <item> Helen Keller </item>
        <item> Mark Twain </item>
        <item> Audre Lorde </item>
        <item> William Shakespeare </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> David Brinkley </item>
        <item> John F. Kennedy </item>
        <item> Herbert Bayard Swope </item>
        <item> Mae West </item>
        <item> Thomas J. Watson </item>
        <item> Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item> Theodore Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Abraham Lincoln </item>
        <item> Lucille Ball </item>
        <item> Mother Theresa </item>
        <item> Joshua J. Marine </item>
        <item> Alexander Graham Bell </item>
        <item> Francis Chan </item>
        <item> Leonardo Da Vinci </item>
        <item> H. Jackson Brown, Jr. </item>
        <item> Anthony Robbins </item>
        <item> J. K Rowling </item>
        <item> Pablo Picasso </item>
        <item> Leo Tolstoy </item>
        <item> Thomas A. Edison </item>
        <item> Albert Einstein </item>
        <item> Dax Shepard </item>
        <item> Elie Wiesel </item>
        <item> Charles Swindoll </item>
        <item> Elie Wiesel </item>
        <item> Henry Ward Beecher </item>
        <item> Harriet Tubman </item>
        <item> Sigmund Freud </item>
        <item> Jim Morrison </item>
        <item> Edgar Allan Poe </item>
        <item> Harriet Tubman </item>
        <item> Babe Ruth </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Ray Bradbury </item>
        <item> David Rockefeller </item>
        <item> Dalai Lama </item>
        <item> Napoleon Hill </item>
        <item> Steve Jobs </item>
        <item> George S. Patton </item>
        <item> Maya Angelou </item>
        <item> Jonathan Swift </item>
        <item> Robert Frost </item>
        <item> Winston Churchill </item>
        <item> Jason Mraz </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Jim Rohn </item>
        <item> Ayn Rand </item>
        <item> Forrest Gump </item>
        <item> Thomas A. Edison </item>
        <item> Bruce Lee </item>
        <item> Bob Dylan </item>
        <item> Bil Keane </item>
        <item> George Bernard Shaw </item>
        <item> Henry Ford </item>
        <item> Denzel Washington </item>
        <item> Ingrid Bergman </item>
        <item> Wayne Gretzky </item>
        <item> Hans Christian Andersen </item>
        <item> Ernest Hemingway </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Aristotle </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> Frank Sinatra </item>
        <item> Joe Namath </item>
        <item> David Viscott </item>
        <item> Robern Frost </item>
        <item> Kurt Vonnegut </item>
        <item> Nathan Hale </item>
        <item> Albert Einstein </item>
        <item> Stephen Hawking </item>
        <item> St. Augustine </item>
        <item> Pablo Picasso </item>
        <item> Salvador Dali </item>
        <item> Søren Kierkegaard </item>
        <item> Leo Burnett </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> George Bernard Shaw </item>
        <item> Lao Tzu </item>
        <item> Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item> Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item> Mother Theresa </item>
        <item> Omar Khayyam </item>
        <item> Gandhi </item>
        <item> Albert Einstein </item>
        <item> Helen Keller </item>
        <item> Robert Frost </item>
        <item> T. S. Eliot </item>
        <item> Abraham Lincoln </item>
        <item> Ray Bradbury </item>
        <item> Steve Jobs </item>
        <item> Mark Twain </item>
        <item> John Muir </item>
        <item> Oprah Winfrey </item>
        <item> Voltaire </item>
        <item> Charles Dickens </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Movie Quotes-->
    <string-array name="movie_Quotes">
        <item>"Don\'we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to us." </item>
        <item>"Great men are not born great, they grow great." </item>
        <item>"Some people can\'t believe in themselves until someone else believes in them first." </item>
        <item>"Life moves pretty fast. If you don\'t stop and look around once in a while, you could miss it." </item>
        <item>"What we do in life echoes in eternity." </item>
        <item>"Every man dies, but not every man really lives." </item>
        <item>"I know what I have to do now. I\'ve got to keep breathing because tomorrow the sun will rise. Who knows what the tide could bring?" </item>
        <item>"No matter what anybody tells you, words and ideas can change the world." </item>
        <item>"Why do we fall sir? So that we can learn to pick ourselves up." </item>
        <item>" You mustn\'t be afraid to dream a little bigger, darling." </item>
        <item>"Sometimes it is the people who no one imagines anything of who do the things that no one can imagine." </item>
        <item>"There should be no boundaries to human endeavor. We are all different. However bad life may seem, there is always something you can do, and succeed at. While there\'s life, there is hope." </item>
        <item>"Two little mice fell in a bucket of cream. The first mouse quickly gave up and drowned. The second mouse, wouldn\'t quit. He struggled so hard that eventually he churned that cream into butter and crawled out. Gentlemen, as of this moment, I am that second mouse." </item>
        <item>"There\'s no such thing as too far. You understand? You push everything as far as you can. You push and you push and you push until it starts pushing back. And then you push some goddamn more." </item>
        <item>"The only thing standing between you and your goal is the bullshit story you keep telling yourself as to why you can\'t achieve it." </item>
        <item>"Here\'s to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They\'re not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can\'t do is ignore them" </item>
        <item>"We buy things we don\'t need, to impress people we don\'t like." </item>
        <item>"Ernest Hemingway once wrote, ‘The world is a fine place and worth fighting for.\' I agree with the second part." </item>
        <item>"What we do in life echoes in eternity." </item>
        <item>"Oh yes, the past can hurt. But, you can either run from it or learn from it." </item>
        <item>"To see the world, things dangerous to come to, to see behind walls, to draw closer, to find each other and to feel. That is the purpose of life." </item>
        <item>"We all end up dead, it\'s just a question of how and why." </item>
        <item>"All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to us." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t ever let somebody tell you can\'t do something, not even me. Alright? You dream, you gotta protect it. People can\'t do something themselves, they wanna tell you can\'t do it. If you want something, go get it. Period." </item>
        <item>"Great men are not born great, they grow great." </item>
        <item>"Remember Red, hope is a good thing, maybe the best of things, and no good thing ever dies." </item>
        <item>"Nobody is gonna hit as hard as life, but it ain\'t how hard you can hit. It\'s how hard you can get hit and keep moving forward. It\'s how much you can take, and keep moving forward. That\'s how winning is done." </item>
        <item>"It is not our abilities that show what we truly are. It is our choices." </item>
        <item>"The closer you are to death, the more alive you feel. It\'s a wonderful way to live. It\'s the only way to drive." </item>
        <item>"You can do anything. You can go anywhere. Money, power is an illusion. It\'s up here. You can be here. Me and you." </item>
        <item>"You cannot live your life to please others. The choice must be yours." </item>
        <item>"Going in one more round when you don\'t think you can – that\'s what makes all the difference in your life." </item>
        <item>"It\'s supposed to be hard. If it wasn\'t hard, everyone would do it. The hard is what makes it great." </item>
        <item>"Sometimes the right path is not the easiest one." </item>
        <item>"Do or Do not. There is no try." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t tell me I can\'t do it; don\'t tell me it can\'t be done!" </item>
        <item>"After a while, you learn to ignore the names people call you and just trust who you are." </item>
        <item>"Calling someone fat doesn\'t make you any skinnier. Calling someone stupid doesn\'t make you any smarter. All you can do in life is try and solve the problem in front of you." </item>
        <item>"All that is gold does not glitter. Not all those who wander are lost." </item>
        <item>"Our lives are defined by opportunities, even the ones we miss." </item>
        <item>"My Mama always said, ‘Life was like a box of chocolates; you never know what you\'re gonna get.'" </item>
        <item>"Find a truly original idea. It is the only way I will ever distinguish myself. It is the only way I will ever matter." </item>
        <item>"Life is not the amount of breaths you take, it\'s the moments that take your breath away." </item>
        <item>"In this life, you don\'t have to prove nothin\' to nobody but yourself. And after what you\'ve gone through, if you haven\'t done that by now, it ain\'t gonna never happen. Now go on back." </item>
        <item>"You have to get lost before you find yourself." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t ever let somebody tell you you can\'t do something, not even me. Alright? You dream, you gotta protect it. People can\'t do something themselves, they wanna tell you you can\'t do it. If you want something, go get it. Period." </item>
        <item>"Do, or do not. There is no" </item>
        <item>"Courage is not the absence of fear but rather the judgment that something is more important than fear." </item>
        <item>"Be deliriously happy or at least leave yourself open to be." </item>
        <item>"Freedom is not just a dream.  It\'s there, beyond those fences that we build all by ourselves." </item>
        <item>"Life moves pretty fast. If you don\'t stop and look around once in a while, you could miss it." </item>
        <item>"The best love is the kind that awakens the soul and makes us reach for more, that plants a fire in our hearts and brings peace to our minds. And that\'s what you\'ve given me. That\'s what I\'d hoped to give you forever." </item>
        <item>"It is not our abilities that show what we truly are… it is our choices." </item>
        <item>"My momma always said," </item>
        <item>"Ah come on, Adrian, it\'s true. I was nobody.  But that don\'t matter either, you know? ‘Cause I was thinkin\', it really don\'t matter if I lose this fight. It really don\'t matter if this guy opens my head, either. ‘Cause all I wanna do is go the distance. Nobody\'s ever gone the distance with Creed, and if I can go that distance, you see, and that bell rings and I\'m still standin\',  I\'m gonna know for the first time in my life, see, that I wasn\'t just another bum from the neighborhood." </item>
        <item>"Every man dies but not every man really lives." </item>
        <item>"All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to us." </item>
        <item>"Nobody is gonna hit as hard as life, but it ain\'t how hard you can hit. It\'s how hard you can get hit and keep moving forward. It\'s how much you can take, and keep moving forward. That\'s how winning\'s done." </item>
        <item>"Somewhere along the line we stopped believing we could do anything. And if we don\'t have our dreams, we have nothing." </item>
        <item>"Me, I still believe in paradise. But now at least I know it\'s not some place you can look for because it\'s not where you go. It\'s how you feel for a moment in your life when you\'re a part of something and if you find that moment, it lasts forever." </item>
        <item>"To find something, anything, a great truth or a lost pair of glasses, you must first believe there will be some advantage in finding it." </item>
        <item>"Remember, kid, there\'s heroes and there\'s legends. Heroes get remembered, but legends never die. Follow your heart kid, and you\'ll never go wrong." </item>
        <item>"Oh yes, the past can hurt. But, you can either run from it or, learn from it." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t tell me I can\'t do it; don\'t tell me it can\'t be done!" </item>
        <item>"You know, the ancient Egyptians had a beautiful belief about death. When their souls got to the entrance to heaven, the guards asked two questions. Their answers determined whether they were able to enter or not. ‘Have you found joy in your life?\' ‘Has your life brought joy to others?" </item>
        <item>"What we do in life echoes in eternity." </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movie_author">
        <item>Chris Gardner </item>
        <item>Gandalf </item>
        <item>Mario Puzo </item>
        <item>Sean Maguire </item>
        <item>Ferris </item>
        <item>Maximus, from Gladiator </item>
        <item>William Wallace, from Braveheart </item>
        <item>from Cast Away </item>
        <item>John Keating, Dead Poets Society </item>
        <item>Alfred, Batman Begins </item>
        <item>Eames, Inception </item>
        <item>Christopher, The Imitation Game </item>
        <item>Stephen Hawking, The Theory of Everything </item>
        <item>Frank Abagnale Sr, Catch Me If You Can </item>
        <item>Walter Abrams, Two For The Money </item>
        <item>Jordan Belfort, Wolf of the Wall Street </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs, Jobs </item>
        <item>Tyler Durden, Fight Club </item>
        <item>William Somerset, Se7en </item>
        <item>Maximus. Gladiator </item>
        <item>Rafiki, The Lion King </item>
        <item>Walter Mitty, The Secret Life of Walter Mitty </item>
        <item>William Wallace, Braveheart </item>
        <item>Gandalf, The Lord of the Rings </item>
        <item>Chris Gardner,  The Pursuit of Happyness </item>
        <item>Vito Corleone, Godfather </item>
        <item>Andy, The Shawshank Redemption </item>
        <item>Rocky Balboa </item>
        <item>Professor Dumbledore, Harry Potter </item>
        <item>James Hunt, Rush </item>
        <item>Christopher McCandless, Into The Wild </item>
        <item>White Queen, Alice In Wonderland </item>
        <item>Rocky Balboa, Rocky IV </item>
        <item>Jimmy Dugan, A league of their own </item>
        <item>Grandmother Willow, Pocahontas </item>
        <item>Yoda, Star Wars – The Empire Strikes Back </item>
        <item>Howard Hughes, The Aviator </item>
        <item>Shrek, Shrek The Third </item>
        <item>Cady, Mean Girls </item>
        <item>Bilbo Baggins, The Lord of the Rings </item>
        <item>Benjamin Button, The Curious Case of Benjamin Button </item>
        <item>Forrest, Forrest Gump </item>
        <item>John Nash, A Beautiful Mind </item>
        <item>Hitch </item>
        <item>Fortune, Rudy </item>
        <item>Margo, Paper Towns </item>
        <item>Chris Gardner, from The Pursuit of Happyness </item>
        <item>Yoda, Star Wars </item>
        <item>The Princess Diaries </item>
        <item>Meet Joe Black </item>
        <item>Instinct </item>
        <item>Ferris, Ferris Bueller’s Day Off </item>
        <item>Nicholas Sparks, The Notebook </item>
        <item>Dumbledore,  Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets </item>
        <item>Life is like a box of chocolates, you never know what you’re gonna get." – Forrest Gump </item>
        <item>Rocky </item>
        <item>Mel Gibson in Braveheart </item>
        <item>Gandalf, Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring </item>
        <item>Rocky </item>
        <item>The Astronaut Farmer </item>
        <item>from The Beach </item>
        <item>from All the King’s Men </item>
        <item>The Sandlot </item>
        <item>The Lion King </item>
        <item>Leonardo Dicaprio in The Aviator </item>
        <item>Carter Chambers, The Bucket List </item>
        <item>Gladiator </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Music Quotes-->
    <string-array name="music_quotes">
        <item>"Music is like a dream. One that I cannot hear." </item>
        <item>"Without music, life would be a mistake" </item>
        <item>"I can chase you, and I can catch you, but there is nothing I can do to make you mine." </item>
        <item>"Music gives a soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination and life to everything." </item>
        <item>"How is it that music can, without words, evoke our laughter, our fears, our highest aspirations?" </item>
        <item>"If I were not a physicist, I would probably be a musician. I often think in music. I live my daydreams in music. I see my life in terms of music." </item>
        <item>"Music is a language that doesn\'t speak in particular words. It speaks in emotions, and if it\'s in the bones, it\'s in the bones." </item>
        <item>"I think music in itself is healing. It\'s an explosive expression of humanity. It\'s something we are all touched by. No matter what culture we\'re from, everyone loves music." </item>
        <item>"One good thing about music, when it hits you, you feel no pain." </item>
        <item>"The only truth is music." </item>
        <item>"There are two means of refuge from the miseries of life: music and cats." </item>
        <item>"Music is the shorthand of emotion." </item>
        <item>"Without music, life would be a blank to me." </item>
        <item>"If music be the food of love, play on, Give me excess of it; that surfeiting, The appetite may sicken, and so die." </item>
        <item>"Music was my refuge. I could crawl into the space between the notes and curl my back to loneliness." </item>
        <item>"After silence, that which comes nearest to expressing the inexpressible is music." </item>
        <item>"The most exciting rhythms seem unexpected and complex, the most beautiful melodies simple and inevitable." </item>
        <item>"Where words fail, music speaks." </item>
        <item>"Music expresses that which cannot be said and on which it is impossible to be silent." </item>
        <item>"We are the music makers, and we are the dreamers of dreams." </item>
        <item>"If I had my life to live over again, I would have made a rule to read some poetry and listen to some music at least once every week." </item>
        <item>"Music produces a kind of pleasure which human nature cannot do without." </item>
        <item>"Music is … A higher revelation than all Wisdom &amp; Philosophy" </item>
        <item>"A man should hear a little music, read a little poetry, and see a fine picture every day of his life, in order that worldly cares may not obliterate the sense of the beautiful which God has implanted in the human soul." </item>
        <item>"Music is to the soul what words are to the mind." </item>
        <item>"Music, once admitted to the soul, becomes a sort of spirit, and never dies." </item>
        <item>"Music touches us emotionally, where words alone can\'t." </item>
        <item>"Virtually every writer I know would rather be a musician." </item>
        <item>"A painter paints pictures on canvas. But musicians paint their pictures on silence." </item>
        <item>"Music . . . can name the unnameable and communicate the unknowable." </item>
        <item>"I like beautiful melodies telling me terrible things." </item>
        <item>"When you make music or write or create, it\'s really your job to have mind-blowing, irresponsible, condomless sex with whatever idea it is you\'re writing about at the time. " </item>
        <item>"If being an egomaniac means I believe in what I do and in my art or music, then in that respect you can call me that… I believe in what I do, and I\'ll say it." </item>
        <item>"Live your truth. Express your love. Share your enthusiasm. Take action towards your dreams. Walk your talk. Dance and sing to your music. Embrace your blessings. Make today worth remembering." </item>
        <item>"Information is not knowledge. Knowledge is not wisdom. Wisdom is not truth. Truth is not beauty. Beauty is not love. Love is not music. Music is THE BEST." </item>
        <item>"Music is the literature of the heart; it commences where speech ends." </item>
        <item>"Beethoven tells you what it\'s like to be Beethoven and Mozart tells you what it\'s like to be human. Bach tells you what it\'s like to be the universe." </item>
        <item>"The music is not in the notes, but in the silence between." </item>
        <item>"Music makes one feel so romantic – at least it always gets on one\'s nerves – which is the same thing nowadays." </item>
        <item>"Without music to decorate it, time is just a bunch of boring production deadlines or dates by which bills must be paid." </item>
        <item>"If you cannot teach me to fly, teach me to sing." </item>
        <item>"Music is the strongest form of magic." </item>
        <item>"Music is the wine that fills the cup of silence." </item>
        <item>"Music is the language of the spirit. It opens the secret of life bringing peace, abolishing strife." </item>
        <item>"Music in the soul can be heard by the universe." </item>
        <item>"Music acts like a magic key, to which the most tightly closed heart opens." </item>
        <item>"Music… will help dissolve your perplexities and purify your character and sensibilities, and in time of care and sorrow, will keep a fountain of joy alive in you." </item>
        <item>"Music is an outburst of the soul." </item>
        <item>"My personal hobbies are reading, listening to music, and silence." </item>
        <item>"Music is the great uniter. An incredible force. Something that people who differ on everything and anything else can have in common." </item>
        <item>"Music produces a kind of pleasure which human nature cannot do without." </item>
        <item>"Music is my higher power" </item>
        <item>"For the first time, he heard something that he knew to be music. He heard people singing. Behind him, across vast distances of space and time, from the place he had left, he thought he heard music too. But perhaps, it was only an echo." </item>
        <item>"It is always fatal to have music or poetry interrupted." </item>
        <item>"Tell me what you listen to, and I\'ll tell you who you are." </item>
        <item>"My heart, which is so full to overflowing, has often been solaced and refreshed by music when sick and weary." </item>
        <item>"No matter how corrupt, greedy, and heartless our government, our corporations, our media, and our religious &amp; charitable institutions may become, the music will still be wonderful." </item>
        <item>"Life seems to go on without effort when I am filled with music." </item>
        <item>"Music is everybody\'s business. It\'s only the publishers who think people own it" </item>
        <item>"Life is like a beautiful melody, only the lyrics are messed up." </item>
        <item>"You have to, take a deep breath. and allow the music to flow through you. Revel in it, allow yourself to awe. When you play allow the music to break your heart with its beauty." </item>
        <item>"Music is an agreeable harmony for the honor of God and the permissible delights of the soul." </item>
        <item>"Music is a proud, temperamental mistress. Give her the time and attention she deserves, and she is yours. Slight her and there will come a day when you call and she will not answer. So I began sleeping less to give her the time she needed." </item>
        <item>"People ask me how I make music. I tell them I just step into it. It\'s like stepping into a river and joining the flow. Every moment in the river has its song." </item>
        <item>"The more you love,the more love you have to give.It\'s the only feeling we have which is infinite…" </item>
        <item>"Music can change the world because it can change people." </item>
        <item>"If music be the food of love, play on." </item>
        <item>"I see my life in terms of music." </item>
        <item>"To me, the greatest pleasure of writing is not what it\'s about, but the music the words make." </item>
        <item>"Musical innovation is full of danger to the State, for when modes of music change, the fundamental laws of the State always change with them." </item>
        <item>"Music could ache and hurt, that beautiful music was a place a suffering man could hide." </item>
        <item>"Music with dinner is an insult both to the cook and the violinist." </item>
        <item>"I\'m just a musical prostitute, my dear." </item>
        <item>"If I cannot fly, let me sing." </item>
        <item>"All the good music has already been written by people with wigs and stuff." </item>
        <item>"Music sounds different to the one who plays it. It is the musician\'s curse." </item>
        <item>"Music is the divine way to tell beautiful, poetic things to the heart.." </item>
        <item>"Everything in me feels fluttering and free, like I could take off from the ground at any second. Music, I think, he makes me feel like music." </item>
        <item>"If Music is a Place — then Jazz is the City, Folk is the Wilderness, Rock is the Road, Classical is a Temple." </item>
        <item>"I love the way music inside a car makes you feel invisible; if you play the stereo at max volume, it\'s almost like the other people can\'t see into your vehicle. It tints your windows, somehow." </item>
        <item>"Film as dream, film as music. No art passes our conscience in the way film does, and goes directly to our feelings, deep down into the dark rooms of our souls." </item>
        <item>"Music brings a warm glow to my vision, thawing mind and muscle from their endless wintering." </item>
        <item>"Softly, deftly, music shall caress you. Hear it, feel it, Secretly possess you." </item>
        <item>"Most people die with their music still locked up inside them." </item>
        <item>"Music is the moonlight in the gloomy night of life." </item>
        <item>"It\'s like if the music is loud enough I won\'t be able to listen to my own thoughts. " </item>
        <item>"There is nothing more to be said or to be done tonight, so hand me over my violin and let us try to forget for half an hour the miserable weather and the still more miserable ways of our fellowmen." </item>
        <item>"The man that hath no music in himself, Nor is not moved with concord of sweet sounds, Is fit for treasons, stratagems, and spoils; The motions of his spirit are dull as night, And his affections dark as Erebus. Let no such man be trusted. Mark the music." </item>
        <item>"To live is to be musical, starting with the blood dancing in your veins. Everything living has a rhythm. Do you feel your music?" </item>
        <item>"Love is friendship set to music." </item>
        <item>"Music, when soft voices die, vibrates in the memory." </item>
        <item>"A great song should lift your heart, warm the soul and make you feel good." </item>
        <item>"But I was not in the band, because I suffer from the kind of tone deafness that is generally associated with actual deafness" </item>
        <item>"When you play, never mind who listens to you." </item>
        <item>"Music, my rampart and my only one." </item>
        <item>"This will be our reply to violence: to make music more intensely, more beautifully, more devotedly than ever before." </item>
        <item>"Music is what tell us that the human race is greater than we realize." </item>
        <item>"If you were music, I would listen to you ceaselessly, and my low spirits would brighten up." </item>
        <item>"I would rather write 10,000 notes than a single letter of the alphabet." </item>
        <item>"I would teach children music, physics, and philosophy; but most importantly music, for the patterns in music and all the arts are the keys to learning." </item>
        <item>"Music gives a soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination" </item>
        <item>"Musical training is a more potent instrument than any other, because rhythm and harmony find their way into the inward places of the soul." </item>
        <item>"Without music, life would be a mistake." </item>
        <item>"Music expresses that which cannot be put into words and that which cannot remain silent." </item>
        <item>"Virtually every writer I know would rather be a musician." </item>
        <item>"Music is what tells us that the human race is greater than we realize." </item>
        <item>"If one should desire to know whether a kingdom is well governed, if its morals are good or bad, the quality of its music will furnish the answer." </item>
        <item>"Music produces a kind of pleasure which human nature cannot do without." </item>
        <item>"If I were not a physicist, I would probably be a musician. I often think in music. I live my daydreams in music. I see my life in terms of music." </item>
        <item>"Life is for the living.Death is for the dead.Let life be like music.And death a note unsaid." </item>
        <item>"After silence, that which comes nearest to expressing the inexpressible is music." </item>
        <item>"The only truth is music." </item>
        <item>"If I had my life to live over again, I would have made a rule to read some poetry and listen to some music at least once every week." </item>
        <item>"Music is the universal language of mankind." </item>
        <item>"Where words fail, music speaks." </item>
        <item>"Life is like a beautiful melody, only the lyrics are messed up." </item>
        <item>"Music is the language of the spirit. It opens the secret of life bringing peace, abolishing strife." </item>
        <item>"Where words leave off, music begins." </item>
        <item>"Music in the soul can be heard by the universe." </item>
        <item>"When I hear music, I fear no danger. I am invulnerable. I see no foe. I am related to the earliest times, and to the latest." </item>
        <item>"Music is the literature of the heart; it commences where speech ends." </item>
        <item>"Without music, life would be a blank to me." </item>
        <item>"You couldn\'t not like someone who liked the guitar." </item>
        <item>"There is no feeling, except the extremes of fear and grief, that does not find relief in music." </item>
        <item>"The most exciting rhythms seem unexpected and complex, the most beautiful melodies simple and inevitable." </item>
        <item>"I would say that music is the easiest means in which to express, but since words are my talent, I must try to express clumsily in words what the pure music would have done better." </item>
        <item>"With the truth, all given facts harmonize; but with what is false, the truth soon hits a wrong note." </item>
        <item>"Music is the shorthand of emotion." </item>
        <item>"Hell is full of musical amateurs." </item>
        <item>"Music is very spiritual, it has the power to bring people together." </item>
        <item>"I think sometimes could I only have music on my own terms, could I live in a great city, and know where I could go whenever I wished the ablution and inundation of musical waves, that were a bath and a medicine." </item>
        <item>"Music is a moral law. It gives soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination, and charm and gaiety to life and to everything." </item>
        <item>"Music in the soul can be heard by the universe." </item>
        <item>"Music doesn\'t lie. If there is something to be changed in this world, then it can only happen through music." </item>
        <item>"Without music, life would be a mistake." </item>
        <item>"Music expresses that which cannot be said and on which it is impossible to be silent." </item>
        <item>" Music is forever; music should grow and mature with you, following you right on up until you die." </item>
        <item>"Life, he realize, was much like a song. In the beginning there is mystery, in the end there is confirmation, but it\'s in the middle where all the emotion resides to make the whole thing worthwhile." </item>
        <item>" I was born with music inside me. Music was one of my parts. Like my ribs, my kidneys, my liver, my heart. Like my blood. It was a force already within me when I arrived on the scene. It was a necessity for me – like food or water." </item>
        <item>"Music should strike fire from the heart of man, and bring tears from the eyes of woman." </item>
        <item>"There is nothing in the world so much like prayer as music is." </item>
        <item>"Music is the mediator between the spiritual and the sensual life." </item>
        <item>"Next to the Word of God, the noble art of music is the greatest treasure in the world." </item>
        <item>"Music was my refuge. I could crawl into the space between the notes and curl my back to loneliness." </item>
        <item>"There are more love songs than anything else. If songs could make you do something we\'d all love one another." </item>
        <item>"I think music in itself is healing. It\'s an explosive expression of humanity. It\'s something we are all touched by. No matter what culture we\'re from, everyone loves music." </item>
        <item>"People haven\'t always been there for me but music always has." </item>
        <item>"Music can change the world because it can change people." </item>
        <item>"Music is the divine way to tell beautiful, poetic things to the heart." </item>
        <item>"Music is the language of the spirit. It opens the secret of life bringing peace, abolishing strife." </item>
        <item>"If I were not a physicist, I would probably be a musician. I often think in music. I live my daydreams in music. I see my life in terms of music." </item>
        <item>"Beautiful music is the art of the prophets that can calm the agitations of the soul; it is one of the most magnificent and delightful presents God has given us." </item>
        <item>"Music is moonlight in the gloomy night of life." </item>
        <item>"Music is the strongest form of magic." </item>
        <item>"You know what music is? God\'s little reminder that there\'s something else besides us in this universe, a harmonic connection between all living beings, every where, even the stars." </item>
        <item>"Music is the great uniter. An incredible force. Something that people who differ on everything and anything else can have in common." </item>
        <item>"Music is the wine that fills the cup of silence." </item>
        <item>"Music washes away from the soul the dust of everyday life." </item>
        <item>" If music be the food of love, play on,Give me excess of it; that surfeiting,The appetite may sicken, and so die. " </item>
        <item>"When I hear music, I fear no danger. I am invulnerable. I see no foe. I am related to the earliest times, and to the latest. " </item>
        <item>"Beethoven tells you what it\'s like to be Beethoven and Mozart tells you what it\'s like to be human. Bach tells you what it\'s like to be the universe." </item>
        <item>"Take a music bath once or twice a week for a few seasons. You will find it is to the soul what a water bath is to the body." </item>
        <item>"The only truth is music." </item>
        <item>"It was the moment I realized what music can do to people, how it can make you hurt and feel so good all at once. " </item>
        <item>"Music is a second language to my heart." </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="music_author">
        <item>Ludwig van Beethoven </item>
        <item>Friedrich Nietzsche </item>
        <item>Morrissey </item>
        <item>Plato </item>
        <item>Jane Swan </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Keith Richards </item>
        <item>Billy Joel </item>
        <item>Bob Marley </item>
        <item>Jack Kerouac </item>
        <item>Albert Schweitzer </item>
        <item>Leo Tolstoy </item>
        <item>Jane Austen </item>
        <item>William Shakespeare </item>
        <item>Maya Angelou </item>
        <item>Aldous Huxley </item>
        <item>W.H. Auden </item>
        <item>Hans Christian Andersen </item>
        <item>Victor Hugo </item>
        <item>Arthur O\'Shaughnessy </item>
        <item>Charles Darwin </item>
        <item>Confucius </item>
        <item>Ludwig van Beethoven </item>
        <item>Johann Wolfgang von Goethe </item>
        <item>Modest Mouse </item>
        <item>Edward Bulwer-Lytton </item>
        <item>Johnny Depp </item>
        <item>Kurt Vonnegut </item>
        <item>Leopold Stokowski </item>
        <item>Leonard Bernstein </item>
        <item>Tom Waits </item>
        <item>Lady Gaga </item>
        <item>John Lennon </item>
        <item>Steve Maraboli </item>
        <item>Frank Zappa </item>
        <item>Alphonse de Lamartine </item>
        <item>Douglas Adams </item>
        <item>Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart </item>
        <item>Oscar Wilde </item>
        <item>Frank Zappa </item>
        <item>J.M. Barrie, Peter Pan </item>
        <item>Marilyn Manson </item>
        <item>Robert Fripp </item>
        <item>Kahlil Gibran </item>
        <item>Lao Tzu </item>
        <item>Maria Augusta von Trapp </item>
        <item>Dietrich Bonhoeffer </item>
        <item>Frederick Delius </item>
        <item>Edith Sitwell </item>
        <item>Sarah Dessen </item>
        <item>Confucius </item>
        <item>Oliver James </item>
        <item>Lois Lowry </item>
        <item>George Eliot </item>
        <item>Tiffanie DeBartolo </item>
        <item>Martin Luther </item>
        <item>Kurt Vonnegut </item>
        <item>George Eliot </item>
        <item>John Lennon </item>
        <item>Hans Christian Andersen </item>
        <item>Kelly White </item>
        <item>Johann Sebastian Bach </item>
        <item>Patrick Rothfuss </item>
        <item>Michael Jackson </item>
        <item>Christina Westover </item>
        <item>Bono </item>
        <item>William Shakespeare </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Truman Capote </item>
        <item>Plato </item>
        <item>Pat Conroy </item>
        <item>G.K. Chesterton </item>
        <item>Freddie Mercury </item>
        <item>Stephen Sondheim </item>
        <item>Frank Zappa </item>
        <item>Patrick Rothfuss </item>
        <item>Pablo Casals </item>
        <item>Lauren Oliver </item>
        <item>Vera Nazarian </item>
        <item>Chuck Klosterman </item>
        <item>Ingmar Bergman </item>
        <item>Haruki Murakami </item>
        <item>Charles Hart </item>
        <item>Benjamin Disraeli </item>
        <item>Jean Paul Friedrich Richter </item>
        <item>Nic Sheff </item>
        <item>Arthur Conan Doyle </item>
        <item>William Shakespeare </item>
        <item>Michael Jackson </item>
        <item>Jackson Pollock </item>
        <item>Percy Bysshe Shelley </item>
        <item>Colbie Caillat </item>
        <item>John Green </item>
        <item>Robert Schumann </item>
        <item>Edna St. Vincent Millay </item>
        <item>Leonard Bernstein </item>
        <item>Napoléon Bonaparte </item>
        <item>Anna Akhmatova </item>
        <item>Ludwig van Beethoven </item>
        <item>  </item>
        <item>Plato </item>
        <item>Plato, The Republic </item>
        <item>Plato, The Republic </item>
        <item>Victor Hugo </item>
        <item>Kurt Vonnegut </item>
        <item>Napoleon Bonaparte </item>
        <item>Confucius </item>
        <item>Confucius </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Langston Hughes, The Collected Poems </item>
        <item>Aldous Huxley, Music at Night and Other Essays </item>
        <item>Jack Kerouac </item>
        <item>Charles Darwin, The Autobiography of Charles Darwin, 1809–82 </item>
        <item>Henry Wadsworth Longfellow </item>
        <item>Hans Christian Andersen </item>
        <item>Hans Christian Andersen </item>
        <item>Kahlil Gibran </item>
        <item>Heinrich Heine </item>
        <item>Lao Tzu </item>
        <item>Henry David Thoreau </item>
        <item>Alphonse de Lamartine </item>
        <item>Jane Austen, Emma </item>
        <item>Stephen King, The Stand </item>
        <item>George Eliot </item>
        <item>W.H. Auden, The Complete Works of W.H. Auden: Prose, Volume III, 1949-1955 </item>
        <item>William Faulkner </item>
        <item>Aristotle, The Nicomachean Ethics </item>
        <item>Leo Tolstoy </item>
        <item>George Bernard Shaw </item>
        <item>Edgar Winter </item>
        <item>Ralph Waldo Emerson </item>
        <item>Plato </item>
        <item>Lao Tzu </item>
        <item>Jimi Hendrix </item>
        <item>Friedrich Nietzsche </item>
        <item>Victor Hugo </item>
        <item>Paul Simon </item>
        <item>Nicholas Sparks </item>
        <item>Ray Charles </item>
        <item>Ludwig van Beethoven </item>
        <item>William P. Merrill </item>
        <item>Ludwig van Beethoven </item>
        <item>Martin Luther </item>
        <item>Maya Angelou </item>
        <item>  –Frank Zappa </item>
        <item>Billy Joel </item>
        <item> Taylor Swift </item>
        <item>Bono </item>
        <item>Pablo Casals </item>
        <item>Khalil Gibran </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Martin Luther </item>
        <item>Jean Paul </item>
        <item>Marilyn Manson </item>
        <item>Robin Williams </item>
        <item>Sarah Dessen, Just Listen </item>
        <item>Robert Fripp </item>
        <item>Berthold Auerbach </item>
        <item>William Shakespeare, Twelfth Night </item>
        <item>Henry David Thoreau </item>
        <item>Douglas Adams </item>
        <item>Oliver Wendell Holmes </item>
        <item>Jack Kerouac </item>
        <item>Nina LaCour, Hold Still </item>
        <item>Mara Arps </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Political Quotes-->
    <string-array name="political_Qutoes">
        <item>A leader is best when people barely know he exists, when his work is done, his aim fulfilled, they will say: we did it ourselves.  </item>
        <item>Where there is no vision, the people perish.  </item>
        <item>I must follow the people. Am I not their leader?  </item>
        <item>You manage things; you lead people.  </item>
        <item>The first responsibility of a leader is to define reality. The last is to say thank you. In between, the leader is a servant.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is the capacity to translate vision into reality.  </item>
        <item>Lead me, follow me, or get out of my way.  </item>
        <item>Before you are a leader, success is all about growing yourself. When you become a leader, success is all about growing others.  </item>
        <item>A leader is a dealer in hope.  </item>
        <item>You don\'t need a title to be a leader.  </item>
        <item>A leader is one who knows the way, goes the way, and shows the way.  </item>
        <item>My own definition of leadership is this: The capacity and the will to rally men and women to a common purpose and the character which inspires confidence.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is lifting a person\'s vision to high sights, the raising of a person\'s performance to a higher standard, the building of a personality beyond its normal limitations.  </item>
        <item>Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, concerned citizens can change world. Indeed it is the only thing that ever has.  </item>
        <item>The nation will find it very hard to look up to the leaders who are keeping their ears to the ground.  </item>
        <item>The most dangerous leadership myth is that leaders are born that there is a genetic factor to leadership. That\'s nonsense; in fact, the opposite is true. Leaders are made rather than born.  </item>
        <item>To command is to serve, nothing more and nothing less.  </item>
        <item>He who has never learned to obey cannot be a good commander.  </item>
        <item>Become the kind of leader that people would follow voluntarily; even if you had no title or position.  </item>
        <item>I start with the premise that the function of leadership is to produce more leaders, not more followers.  </item>
        <item>Effective leadership is not about making speeches or being liked; leadership is defined by results not attributes.  </item>
        <item>Anyone can hold the helm when the sea is calm.  </item>
        <item>A great person attracts great people and knows how to hold them together.  </item>
        <item>The best executive is the one who has sense enough to pick good men to do what he wants done, and self-restraint enough to keep from meddling with them while they do it.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is influence.  </item>
        <item>You don\'t lead by pointing and telling people some place to go. You lead by going to that place and making a case.  </item>
        <item>When I give a minister an order, I leave it to him to find the means to carry it out.  </item>
        <item>Men make history and not the other way around. In periods where there is no leadership, society stands still. Progress occurs when courageous, skillful leaders seize the opportunity to change things for the better.  </item>
        <item>People buy into the leader before they buy into the vision.  </item>
        <item>So much of what we call management consists in making it difficult for people to work.  </item>
        <item>The art of leadership is saying no, not saying yes. It is very easy to say yes.  </item>
        <item>The very essence of leadership is that you have to have a vision. It\'s got to be a vision you articulate clearly and forcefully on every occasion. You can\'t blow an uncertain trumpet.  </item>
        <item>The key to successful leadership today is influence, not authority.  </item>
        <item>A good general not only sees the way to victory; he also knows when victory is impossible.  </item>
        <item>A great leader\'s courage to fulfill his vision comes from passion, not position.  </item>
        <item>A leader takes people where they want to go. A great leader takes people where they don\'t necessarily want to go, but ought to be.  </item>
        <item>The challenge of leadership is to be strong, but not rude; be kind, but not weak; be bold, but not bully; be thoughtful, but not lazy; be humble, but not timid; be proud, but not arrogant; have humor, but without folly.  </item>
        <item>Outstanding leaders go out of their way to boost the self-esteem of their personnel. If people believe in themselves, it\'s amazing what they can accomplish.  </item>
        <item>A true leader has the confidence to stand alone, the courage to make tough decisions, and the compassion to listen to the needs of others. He does not set out to be a leader, but becomes one by the equality of his actions and the integrity of his intent.  </item>
        <item>A ruler should be slow to punish and swift to reward.  </item>
        <item>No man will make a great leader who wants to do it all himself, or to get all the credit for doing it.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is the art of getting someone else to do something you want done because he wants to do it.  </item>
        <item>The leader has to be practical and a realist yet must talk the language of the visionary and the idealist.  </item>
        <item>Leaders think and talk about the solutions. Followers think and talk about the problems.  </item>
        <item>A man who wants to lead the orchestra must turn his back on the crowd.  </item>
        <item>Never tell people how to do things. Tell them what to do and they will surprise you with their ingenuity.  </item>
        <item>As we look ahead into the next century, leaders will be those who empower others.  </item>
        <item>All of the great leaders have had one characteristic in common: it was the willingness to confront unequivocally the major anxiety of their people in their time. This, and not much else, is the essence of leadership.  </item>
        <item>Do what you feel in your heart to be right for you\'ll be criticized anyway.  </item>
        <item>Don\'t necessarily avoid sharp edges. Occasionally they are necessary to leadership.  </item>
        <item>Education is the mother of leadership.  </item>
        <item>Effective leadership is putting first things first. Effective management is discipline, carrying it out.  </item>
        <item>Great leaders are almost always great simplifiers, who can cut through argument, debate, and doubt to offer a solution everybody can understand.  </item>
        <item>Great leaders are not defined by the absence of weakness, but rather by the presence of clear strengths.  </item>
        <item>He who has great power should use it lightly.  </item>
        <item>He who has learned how to obey will know how to command.  </item>
        <item>I am reminded how hollow the label of leadership sometimes is and how heroic followership can be.  </item>
        <item>I cannot give you the formula for success, but I can give you the formula for failure, which is: Try to please everybody.  </item>
        <item>If one is lucky, a solitary fantasy can totally transform one million realities.  </item>
        <item>If you would not be forgotten, as soon as you are dead and rotten, either write things worth reading, or do things worth the writing.  </item>
        <item>If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader.  </item>
        <item>In matters of style, swim with the current; in matters of principle, stand like a rock.  </item>
        <item>It is absurd that a man should rule others, who cannot rule himself.  </item>
        <item>It is better to lead from behind and to put others in front, especially when you celebrate victory when nice things occur. You take the front line when there is danger. Then people will appreciate your leadership.  </item>
        <item>Lead and inspire people. Don\'t try to manage and manipulate people. Inventories can be managed but people must be led.  </item>
        <item>Leaders aren\'t born, they are made. And they are made just like anything else, through hard work. And that\'s the price we\'ll have to pay to achieve that goal, or any goal.  </item>
        <item>Leaders must be close enough to relate to others, but far enough ahead to motivate them.  </item>
        <item>Leadership and learning are indispensable to each other.  </item>
        <item>Leadership cannot just go along to get along. Leadership must meet the moral challenge of the day.  </item>
        <item>Leadership does not always wear the harness of compromise.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is a potent combination of strategy and character. But if you must be without one, be without the strategy.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is solving problems. The day soldiers stop bringing you their problems is the day you have stopped leading them. They have either lost confidence that you can help or concluded you do not care. Either case is a failure of leadership.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is the key to 99 percent of all successful efforts.  </item>
        <item>Leadership is unlocking people\'s potential to become better.  </item>
        <item>Management is about arranging and telling. Leadership is about nurturing and enhancing.  </item>
        <item>Management is efficiency in climbing the ladder of success; leadership determines whether the ladder is leaning against the right wall.  </item>
        <item>Never give an order that can\'t be obeyed.  </item>
        <item>No man is good enough to govern another man without that other\'s consent.  </item>
        <item>What you do has far greater impact than what you say.  </item>
        <item>Not the cry, but the flight of a wild duck, leads the flock to fly and follow.  </item>
        <item>One of the tests of leadership is the ability to recognize a problem before it becomes an emergency.  </item>
        <item>The final test of a leader is that he leaves behind him in other men, the conviction and the will to carry on.  </item>
        <item>The greatest leaders mobilize others by coalescing people around a shared vision.  </item>
        <item>The growth and development of people is the highest calling of leadership.  </item>
        <item>To do great things is difficult; but to command great things is more difficult.  </item>
        <item>To have long term success as a coach or in any position of leadership, you have to be obsessed in some way.  </item>
        <item>True leadership lies in guiding others to success. In ensuring that everyone is performing at their best, doing the work they are pledged to do and doing it well.  </item>
        <item>We live in a society obsessed with public opinion. But leadership has never been about popularity.  </item>
        <item>Whatever you are, be a good one.  </item>
        <item>You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You must do the thing you think you cannot do.  </item>
        <item>A competent leader can get efficient service from poor troops, while on the contrary an incapable leader can demoralize the best of troops.  </item>
        <item>A good leader is a person who takes a little more than his share of the blame and a little less than his share of the credit.  </item>
        <item>There are three essentials to leadership: humility, clarity and courage.  </item>
        <item>I am endlessly fascinated that playing football is considered a training ground for leadership, but raising children isn\'t.  </item>
        <item>A cowardly leader is the most dangerous of men.  </item>
        <item>My responsibility is getting all my players playing for the name on the front of the jersey, not the one on the back.  </item>
        <item>A good plan violently executed now is better than a perfect plan executed next week.  </item>
        <item>The supreme quality of leadership is integrity.  </item>
        <item>You don\'t lead by hitting people over the head that\'s assault, not leadership. </item>
        <item>Earn your leadership every day.  </item>
        <item>"I have come to the conclusion that politics are too serious a matter to be left to the politicians." </item>
        <item>"We are not interested in the possibilities of defeat; they do not exist." </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="political_Author">
        <item> Lao Tzu </item>
        <item> Proverbs 29:18 </item>
        <item> Benjamin Disraeli </item>
        <item> Rear Admiral Grace Murray Hopper </item>
        <item> Max DePree </item>
        <item> Warren Bennis </item>
        <item>  General George Patton </item>
        <item> Jack Welch </item>
        <item> Napoleon Bonaparte </item>
        <item> Multiple Attributions </item>
        <item> John Maxwell </item>
        <item> General Montgomery </item>
        <item> Peter Drucker </item>
        <item> Margaret Mead </item>
        <item> Sir Winston Churchill </item>
        <item> Warren Bennis </item>
        <item> Andre Malraux </item>
        <item> Aristotle </item>
        <item> Brian Tracy </item>
        <item> Ralph Nader </item>
        <item> Peter Drucker </item>
        <item> Publilius Syrus </item>
        <item> Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe </item>
        <item> Theodore Roosevelt </item>
        <item> John C. Maxwell </item>
        <item> Ken Kesey </item>
        <item> Napoleon Bonaparte </item>
        <item> Harry S. Truman </item>
        <item> John Maxwell </item>
        <item> Peter Drucker </item>
        <item> Tony Blair </item>
        <item> Reverend Theodore Hesburgh </item>
        <item> Kenneth Blanchard </item>
        <item> Polybius </item>
        <item> John Maxwell </item>
        <item> Rosalynn Carter </item>
        <item> Jim Rohn </item>
        <item> Sam Walton </item>
        <item> Douglas MacArthur </item>
        <item> Ovid </item>
        <item> Andrew Carnegie </item>
        <item> General Dwight Eisenhower </item>
        <item> Eric Hoffer </item>
        <item> Brian Tracy </item>
        <item> Max Lucado </item>
        <item> General George Patton </item>
        <item> Bill Gates </item>
        <item> John Kenneth Galbraith </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> Donald Rumsfeld </item>
        <item> Wendell Willkie </item>
        <item> Stephen Covey </item>
        <item> General Colin Powell </item>
        <item> John Zenger </item>
        <item> Seneca </item>
        <item> Solon </item>
        <item> Warren Bennis </item>
        <item> Herbert Swope </item>
        <item> Maya Angelou </item>
        <item> Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item> John Quincy Adams </item>
        <item> Thomas Jefferson </item>
        <item> Latin Proverb </item>
        <item> Nelson Mandela </item>
        <item> Ross Perot </item>
        <item> Vince Lombardi </item>
        <item> John C. Maxwell </item>
        <item> John F. Kennedy </item>
        <item> Jesse Jackson </item>
        <item> Woodrow Wilson </item>
        <item> Norman Schwarzkopf </item>
        <item> Colin Powell </item>
        <item> Erskine Bowles </item>
        <item> Bill Bradley </item>
        <item> Tom Peters </item>
        <item> Stephen Covey </item>
        <item> General Douglas MacArthur </item>
        <item> Abraham Lincoln </item>
        <item> Stephen Covey </item>
        <item> Chinese Proverb </item>
        <item> Arnold Glasow </item>
        <item> Walter Lippman </item>
        <item> Ken Blanchard </item>
        <item> Harvey Firestone </item>
        <item> Friedrich Nietzsche </item>
        <item> Pat Riley </item>
        <item> Bill Owens </item>
        <item> Marco Rubio </item>
        <item> Abraham Lincoln </item>
        <item> Eleanor Roosevelt </item>
        <item> John J Pershing </item>
        <item> John Maxwell </item>
        <item> Fuchan Yuan </item>
        <item> Dee Dee Myers </item>
        <item> Stephen King </item>
        <item> Unknown </item>
        <item> George Patton </item>
        <item> Dwight Eisenhower </item>
        <item> Dwight Eisenhower </item>
        <item> Michael Jordan </item>
        <item> Charles De Gaulle </item>
        <item> Queen Victoria </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Reading_writing Quotes-->
    <string-array name="reading_writing_quotes">
        <item>“Read a thousand books, and your words will flow like a river.” </item>
        <item>“The first draft is just you telling yourself the story.” </item>
        <item>“You don\'t start out writing good stuff. You start out writing crap and thinking it\'s good stuff, and then gradually you get better at it. That\'s why I say one of the most valuable traits is persistence.” </item>
        <item>“You can always edit a bad page. You can\'t edit a blank page.” </item>
        <item>“Start writing, no matter what. The water does not flow until the faucet is turned on.” </item>
        <item>“Every secret of a writer\'s soul, every experience of his life, every quality of his mind, is written large in his works.” </item>
        <item>“And by the way, everything in life is writable about if you have the outgoing guts to do it, and the imagination to improvise. The worst enemy to creativity is self-doubt.” </item>
        <item>“Don\'t tell me the moon is shining; show me the glint of light on broken glass.” </item>
        <item>“When your story is ready for rewrite, cut it to the bone. Get rid of every ounce of excess fat. This is going to hurt; revising a story down to the bare essentials is always a little like murdering children, but it must be done.” </item>
        <item>Everybody walks past a thousand story ideas every day. The good writers are the ones who see five or six of them. Most people don\'t see any. </item>
        <item>“There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you.” </item>
        <item>“Don\'t bend; don\'t water it down; don\'t try to make it logical; don\'t edit your own soul according to the fashion. Rather, follow your most intense obsessions mercilessly.” </item>
        <item>“If the book is true, it will find an audience that is meant to read it.” </item>
        <item>I think all writing is a disease. You can\'t stop it.” </item>
        <item>“I can shake off everything as I write; my sorrows disappear, my courage is reborn.” </item>
        <item>A professional writer is an amateur who didn\'t quit.” </item>
        <item>“People say, ‘What advice do you have for people who want to be writers?\' I say, they don\'t really need advice, they know they want to be writers, and they\'re gonna do it. Those people who know that they really want to do this and are cut out for it, they know it.” </item>
        <item>“I believe myself that a good writer doesn\'t really need to be told anything except to keep at it.” </item>
        <item>"You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." </item>
        <item>"If you don\'t have time to read, you don\'t have the time (or the tools) to write. Simple as that." </item>
        <item>"We write to taste life twice, in the moment and in retrospect." </item>
        <item>"Substitute \'damn\' every time you\'re inclined to write \'very;\' your editor will delete it and the writing will be just as it should be." </item>
        <item>"If there\'s a book that you want to read, but it hasn\'t been written yet, then you must write it." </item>
        <item>"One day I will find the right words, and they will be simple." </item>
        <item>"Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing." </item>
        <item>"You never have to change anything you got up in the middle of the night to write." </item>
        <item>"No tears in the writer, no tears in the reader. No surprise in the writer, no surprise in the reader." </item>
        <item>"Read, read, read. Read everything -- trash, classics, good and bad, and see how they do it. Just like a carpenter who works as an apprentice and studies the master. Read! You\'ll absorb it. Then write. If it\'s good, you\'ll find out. If it\'s not, throw it out of the window." </item>
        <item>"You must stay drunk on writing so reality cannot destroy you." </item>
        <item>"Words can be like X-rays if you use them properly -- they\'ll go through anything. You read and you\'re pierced." </item>
        <item>"How vain it is to sit down to write when you have not stood up to live." </item>
        <item>"I can shake off everything as I write; my sorrows disappear, my courage is reborn." </item>
        <item>"A writer is someone for whom writing is more difficult than it is for other people." </item>
        <item>"Let me live, love, and say it well in good sentences." </item>
        <item>"Here is a lesson in creative writing. First rule: Do not use semicolons. They are transvestite hermaphrodites representing absolutely nothing. All they do is show you\'ve been to college." </item>
        <item>"Don\'t bend; don\'t water it down; don\'t try to make it logical; don\'t edit your own soul according to the fashion. Rather, follow your most intense obsessions mercilessly." </item>
        <item>"I kept always two books in my pocket, one to read, one to write in." </item>
        <item>"You can make anything by writing." </item>
        <item>"A word after a word after a word is power." </item>
        <item>"Tears are words that need to be written." </item>
        <item>"You should write because you love the shape of stories and sentences and the creation of different words on a page. Writing comes from reading, and reading is the finest teacher of how to write." </item>
        <item>"Writing is like sex. First you do it for love, then you do it for your friends, and then you do it for money." </item>
        <item>"To survive, you must tell stories." </item>
        <item>"Always be a poet, even in prose." </item>
        <item>"If my doctor told me I had only six minutes to live, I wouldn\'t brood. I\'d type a little faster." </item>
        <item>"The purpose of a writer is to keep civilization from destroying itself." </item>
        <item>"I write to discover what I know." </item>
        <item>"Ideas are like rabbits. You get a couple and learn how to handle them, and pretty soon you have a dozen." </item>
        <item>"A book is made from a tree. It is an assemblage of flat, flexible parts (still called "leaves") imprinted with dark pigmented squiggles. One glance at it and you hear the voice of another person, perhaps someone dead for thousands of years. Across the millennia, the author is speaking, clearly and silently, inside your head, directly to you. Writing is perhaps the greatest of human inventions, binding together people, citizens of distant epochs, who never knew one another. Books break the shackles of time--proof that humans can work magic." </item>
        <item>"Words do not express thoughts very well. They always become a little different immediately after they are expressed, a little distorted, a little foolish." </item>
        <item>"Writing books is the closest men ever come to childbearing." </item>
        <item>"Find out the reason that commands you to write; see whether it has spread its roots into the very depth of your heart; confess to yourself you would have to die if you were forbidden to write." </item>
        <item>"As a writer, you should not judge, you should understand." </item>
        <item>"A good writer possesses not only his own spirit but also the spirit of his friends." </item>
        <item>"The most valuable of all talents is that of never using two words when one will do." </item>
        <item>"If it sounds like writing, I rewrite it. Or, if proper usage gets in the way, it may have to go. I can\'t allow what we learned in English composition to disrupt the sound and rhythm of the narrative." </item>
        <item>"Writers live twice." </item>
        <item>"To produce a mighty book, you must choose a mighty theme." </item>
        <item>"Words are a lens to focus one\'s mind." </item>
        <item>"I am irritated by my own writing. I am like a violinist whose ear is true, but whose fingers refuse to reproduce precisely the sound he hears within." </item>
        <item>"Writing is its own reward." </item>
        <item>"A blank piece of paper is God\'s way of telling us how hard it is to be God." </item>
        <item>"I went for years not finishing anything. Because, of course, when you finish something you can be judged." </item>
        <item>"I love deadlines. I like the whooshing sound they make as they fly by." </item>
        <item>"Half my life is an act of revision." </item>
        <item>"Get it down. Take chances. It may be bad, but it\'s the only way you can do anything really good." </item>
        <item>"Almost anyone can be an author; the business is to collect money and fame from this state of being." </item>
        <item>“A good novel tells us the truth about its hero; but a bad novel tells us the truth about its author.” </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="reading_writing_author">
        <item>Lisa See </item>
        <item>Terry Pratchett </item>
        <item>Octavia E. Butler </item>
        <item>Jodi Picoult </item>
        <item>Louis L’Amour </item>
        <item> Virginia Woolf </item>
        <item>Sylvia Plath </item>
        <item>Anton Chekhov </item>
        <item>Stephen King </item>
        <item>Orson Scott </item>
        <item>Maya Angelou </item>
        <item>Franz Kafka </item>
        <item>Wally Lamb </item>
        <item>William Carlos Williams </item>
        <item>Anne Frank </item>
        <item>Richard Bach </item>
        <item>R.L. Stine </item>
        <item>Chinua Achebe </item>
        <item>Madeleine L\'Engle </item>
        <item>Stephen King </item>
        <item>Anaïs Nin </item>
        <item>Mark Twain </item>
        <item>Toni Morrison </item>
        <item>Jack Kerouac, The Dharma Bums </item>
        <item>Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item>Saul Bellow </item>
        <item>Robert Frost </item>
        <item>William Faulkner </item>
        <item>Ray Bradbury, Zen in the Art of Writing </item>
        <item>Aldous Huxley, Brave New World </item>
        <item>Henry David Thoreau </item>
        <item>Anne Frank </item>
        <item>Thomas Mann, Essays of Three Decades </item>
        <item>Sylvia Plath, The Unabridged Journals of Sylvia Plath </item>
        <item>Kurt Vonnegut Jr., A Man Without a Country </item>
        <item>Franz Kafka </item>
        <item>Robert Louis Stevenson </item>
        <item>C.S. Lewis </item>
        <item>Margaret Atwood </item>
        <item>Paulo Coelho </item>
        <item>Annie Proulx </item>
        <item>Virginia Woolf </item>
        <item>Umberto Eco, The Island of the Day Before </item>
        <item>Charles Baudelaire </item>
        <item>Isaac Asimov </item>
        <item>Albert Camus </item>
        <item>Flannery O\'Connor </item>
        <item>John Steinbeck </item>
        <item>Carl Sagan </item>
        <item>Hermann Hesse </item>
        <item>Norman Mailer </item>
        <item>Rainer Maria Rilke </item>
        <item>Ernest Hemingway </item>
        <item>Friedrich Nietzsche </item>
        <item>Thomas Jefferson </item>
        <item>Elmore Leonard </item>
        <item> Natalie Goldberg </item>
        <item>Herman Melville </item>
        <item> Ayn Rand </item>
        <item>Gustave Flaubert </item>
        <item>Henry Miller </item>
        <item>Sidney Sheldon </item>
        <item>Erica Jong </item>
        <item>Douglas Adams </item>
        <item>John Irving </item>
        <item>William Faulkner </item>
        <item>A. A. Milne </item>
        <item>  </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Sport Quotes-->
    <string-array name="sport_quotes">
        <item>“The only way to prove that you\'re a good sport is to lose.” </item>
        <item>“Only he who can see the invisible can do the impossible.” </item>
        <item>“When you\'re riding, only the race in which you\'re riding is important.” </item>
        <item>“Age is no barrier. It\'s a limitation you put on your mind.” </item>
        <item>“I always felt that my greatest asset was not my physical ability, it was my mental ability.” </item>
        <item>“A trophy carries dust. Memories last forever.” </item>
        <item>“Number one is just to gain a passion for running. To love the morning, to love the trail, to love the pace on the track. And if some kid gets really good at it, that\'s cool too.” </item>
        <item>“Most people give up just when they\'re about to achieve success. They quit on the one yard line. They give up at the last minute of the game one foot from a winning touchdown.” </item>
        <item>“You have to do something in your life that is honorable and not cowardly if you are to live in peace with yourself.” </item>
        <item>“There may be people that have more talent than you, but theres no excuse for anyone to work harder than you do.” </item>
        <item>“Baseball is the only field of endeavor where a man can succeed three times out of ten and be considered a good performer.” </item>
        <item>“One man practicing sportsmanship is far better than 50 preaching it.” </item>
        <item>“The five S\'s of sports training are: stamina, speed, strength, skill, and spirit; but the greatest of these is spirit.” </item>
        <item>An athlete cannot run with money in his pockets. He must run with hope in his heart and dreams in his head.” </item>
        <item>“Somewhere behind the athlete you\'ve become and the hours of practice and the coaches who have pushed you is a little girl who fell in love with the game and never looked back… play for her.” </item>
        <item>“When you\'ve got something to prove, there\'s nothing greater than a challenge.” </item>
        <item>“Never give up, never give in, and when the upper hand is ours, may we have the ability to handle the win with the dignity that we absorbed the loss.” </item>
        <item>“It\'s not the will to win that matters—everyone has that. It\'s the will to prepare to win that matters.” </item>
        <item>“Persistence can change failure into extraordinary achievement.” </item>
        <item>“I\'ve learned that something constructive comes from every defeat.” </item>
        <item>“Make sure your worst enemy doesn\'t live between your own two ears.” </item>
        <item>“Set your goals high, and don\'t stop till you get there.” </item>
        <item>“I became a good pitcher when I stopped trying to make them miss the ball and started trying to make them hit it.” </item>
        <item>“If you can\'t outplay them, outwork them.” </item>
        <item>“People ask me what I do in winter when there\'s no baseball. I\'ll tell you what I do. I stare out the window and wait for spring.” </item>
        <item>“Most people never run far enough on their first wind to find out they\'ve got a second.” </item>
        <item>“Do you know what my favorite part of the game is? The opportunity to play.” </item>
        <item>“If at first you don\'t succeed, you are running about average.” </item>
        <item>“Continuous effort — not strength or intelligence — is the key to unlocking our potential.” </item>
        <item>“Good is not good when better is expected.” </item>
        <item>“The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person\'s determination.” </item>
        <item>“Champions keep playing until they get it right.” </item>
        <item>“You were born to be a player. You were meant to be here. This moment is yours.” </item>
        <item>“What you lack in talent can be made up with desire, hustle, and giving 110 percent all the time.” </item>
        <item>“If you fail to prepare, you\'re prepared to fail.” </item>
        <item>“How you respond to the challenge in the second half will determine what you become after the game, whether you are a winner or a loser.” </item>
        <item>“Persistence can change failure into extraordinary achievement.” </item>
        <item>“Sports serve society by providing vivid examples of excellence.” </item>
        <item>“The principle is competing against yourself. It\'s about self-improvement, about being better than you were the day before.” </item>
        <item>“The road to Easy Street goes through the sewer.” </item>
        <item>“You are never really playing an opponent. You are playing yourself, your own highest standards, and when you reach your limits, that is real joy.” </item>
        <item>“What makes something special is not just what you have to gain, but what you feel there is to lose.” </item>
        <item>“The more difficult the victory, the greater the happiness in winning.” </item>
        <item>“One man can be a crucial ingredient on a team, but one man cannot make a team.” </item>
        <item>“Nobody who ever gave his best regretted it.” </item>
        <item>“Stubbornness usually is considered a negative; but I think that trait has been a positive for me.” </item>
        <item>“You\'ve got to take the initiative and play your game. In a decisive set, confidence is the difference.” </item>
        <item>“When you win, say nothing, when you lose, say less.” </item>
        <item>“The hardest skill to acquire in this sport is the one where you compete all out, give it all you have, and you are still getting beat no matter what you do. When you have the killer instinct to fight through that, it is very special.” </item>
        <item>“The mind is the limit. As long as the mind can envision the fact that you can do something, you can do it, as long as you really believe 100 percent.” </item>
        <item>“When I go out there, I have no pity on my brother. I am out there to win.” </item>
        <item>“During my 18 years I came to bat almost 10,000 times. I struck out about 1,700 times and walked maybe 1,800 times. You figure a ballplayer will average about 500 at bats a season. That means I played seven years without ever hitting the ball.” </item>
        <item>“I never left the field saying I could have done more to get ready and that gives me piece of mind.” </item>
        <item>“Leadership, like coaching, is fighting for the hearts and souls of men and getting them to believe in you.” </item>
        <item>“You win some, you lose some, and some get rained out, but you gotta suit up for them all.” </item>
        <item>“Always make a total effort, even when the odds are against you.” </item>
        <item>“Most talented players don\'t always succeed. Some don\'t even make the team. It\'s more what\'s inside.” </item>
        <item>“You have to expect things of yourself before you can do them.” </item>
        <item>“To uncover your true potential you must first find your own limits and then you have to have the courage to blow past them.” </item>
        <item>“Show me a guy who\'s afraid to look bad, and I\'ll show you a guy you can beat every time.” </item>
        <item>“You can motivate by fear, and you can motivate by reward. But both those methods are only temporary. The only lasting thing is self motivation.” </item>
        <item>“You find that you have peace of mind and can enjoy yourself, get more sleep, and rest when you know that it was a one hundred percent effort that you gave–win or lose.” </item>
        <item>“My motto was always to keep swinging. Whether I was in a slump or feeling badly or having trouble off the field, the only thing to do was keep swinging.” </item>
        <item>“I didn\'t believe in team motivation. I believe in getting a team prepared so it knows it will have the necessary confidence when it steps on the field and be prepared to play a good game.” </item>
        <item>“If you train hard, you\'ll not only be hard, you\'ll be hard to beat.” </item>
        <item>“Your biggest opponent isn\'t the other guy. It\'s human nature.” </item>
        <item>“If you can believe it, the mind can achieve it.” </item>
        <item>“Without self-discipline, success is impossible, period.” </item>
        <item>“If you don\'t have confidence, you\'ll always find a way not to win.” </item>
        <item>“Obstacles don\'t have to stop you. If you run into a wall, don\'t turn around and give up. Figure out how to climb it, go through it, or work around it.” </item>
        <item>“Make each day your masterpiece.” </item>
        <item>“Excellence is the gradual result of always striving to do better.” </item>
        <item>“Win If You Can, Lose If You Must, But NEVER QUIT!” </item>
        <item>“Do you know what my favorite part of the game is? The opportunity to play.” </item>
        <item>“If you have everything under control, you\'re not moving fast enough.” </item>
        <item>“Just keep going. Everybody gets better if they keep at it.” </item>
        <item>“What do do with a mistake: recognize it, admit it, learn from it, forget it.” </item>
        <item>“Push yourself again and again. Don\'t give an inch until the final buzzer sounds.” </item>
        <item>“If you aren\'t going all the way, why go at all?” </item>
        <item>“You can\'t put a limit on anything. The more you dream, the farther you get.” </item>
        <item>“Do not let what you can not do interfere with what you can do.” </item>
        <item>“Pain is temporary. It may last a minute, or an hour, or a day, or a year, but eventually it will subside and something else will take its place. If I quit, however, it lasts forever.” </item>
        <item>“Wisdom is always an overmatch for strength.” </item>
        <item>“The will to win is important, but the will to prepare is vital.” </item>
        <item>“Adversity cause some men to break; others to break records.” </item>
        <item>“Never let your head hang down. Never give up and sit down and grieve. Find another way.” </item>
        <item>“Some people say I have attitude – maybe I do…but I think you have to. You have to believe in yourself when no one else does – that makes you a winner right there. ” </item>
        <item>“Never let the fear of striking out get in your way.” </item>
        <item>“It is not the size of a man but the size of his heart that matters.” </item>
        <item>“I hated every minute of training, but I said, ‘Don\'t quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion.\'” </item>
        <item>“There are only two options regarding commitment. You\'re either IN or you\'re OUT. There is no such thing as life in-between.” </item>
        <item>“A champion is someone who gets up when he can\'t.” </item>
        <item>“It ain\'t over till it\'s over.” </item>
        <item>“You\'re never a loser until you quit trying.” </item>
        <item>“Never give up! Failure and rejection are only the first step to succeeding.” </item>
        <item>“You miss 100 percent of the shots you don\'t take.” </item>
        <item>“The highest compliment that you can pay me is to say that I work hard every day, that I never dog it.” </item>
        <item>“Gold medals aren\'t really made of gold. They\'re made of sweat, determination, and a hard-to-find alloy called guts.” </item>
        <item>“I\'ve missed more than 9,000 shots in my career. I\'ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I\'ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I\'ve failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed.” </item>
        <item>“It\'s not whether you get knocked down; it\'s whether you get up.” </item>
        <item>“When someone comes along and expresses him or herself as freely as they think, people flock to it. They enjoy it.” </item>
        <item>“I\'m obsessed with extreme winners cause I think there\'s a madness to it. I truly believe that in order to truly be great at something you need to give it a certain amount of madness.” </item>
        <item>“Once you understand what excellence is all about…you see how excellence manifests itself in any discipline.” </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sport_author">
        <item>Ernie Banks </item>
        <item>Frank L. Gaines </item>
        <item>Bill Shoemaker </item>
        <item>Jackie Joyner-Kersee </item>
        <item>Bruce Jenner </item>
        <item>Mary Lou Retton </item>
        <item>Pat Tyson </item>
        <item>Ross Perot </item>
        <item>Larry Brown </item>
        <item>Derek Jeter </item>
        <item>Ted Williams </item>
        <item>Knute Rockne </item>
        <item>Ken Doherty </item>
        <item>Emil Zatopek </item>
        <item>Mia Hamm </item>
        <item>Terry Bradshaw </item>
        <item>Doug Williams </item>
        <item>Paul “Bear” Bryant </item>
        <item>Marv Levy </item>
        <item>Tom Landry </item>
        <item>Laird Hamilton </item>
        <item>Bo Jackson </item>
        <item>Sandy Koufax </item>
        <item>Ben Hogan </item>
        <item>Rogers Hornsby </item>
        <item>William James </item>
        <item>Mike Singletary </item>
        <item>M.H. Alderson </item>
        <item>Liane Cardes </item>
        <item>Vin Scully </item>
        <item>Tommy Lasorda </item>
        <item>Billie Jean King </item>
        <item>Herb Brooks </item>
        <item>Don Zimmer </item>
        <item>Mark Spitz </item>
        <item>Lou Holtz </item>
        <item>Matt Biondi </item>
        <item>George F. Will </item>
        <item>Steve Young </item>
        <item>John Madden </item>
        <item>Arthur Ashe </item>
        <item>Andre Agassi </item>
        <item>Pele </item>
        <item>Kareem Abdul-Jabbar </item>
        <item>George Halas </item>
        <item>Cal Ripken Jr. </item>
        <item>Chris Evert </item>
        <item>Paul Brown </item>
        <item>Eddie Reese </item>
        <item>Arnold Schwarzenegger </item>
        <item>Joe Frazier </item>
        <item>Mickey Mantle </item>
        <item>Peyton Manning </item>
        <item>Eddie Robinson </item>
        <item>J. Askenberg </item>
        <item>Arnold Palmer </item>
        <item>Brett Favre </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan </item>
        <item>Picabo Street </item>
        <item>Lou Brock </item>
        <item>Homer Rice </item>
        <item>Gordie Howe </item>
        <item>Hank Aaron </item>
        <item>Tom Landry </item>
        <item>Herschel Walker </item>
        <item>Bobby Knight </item>
        <item>Ronnie Lott </item>
        <item>Lou Holtz </item>
        <item>Carl Lewis </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan </item>
        <item>John Wooden </item>
        <item>Pat Riley </item>
        <item>Cameron Trammell </item>
        <item>Mike Singletary </item>
        <item>Mario Andretti </item>
        <item>Ted Williams </item>
        <item>Dean Smith </item>
        <item>Larry Bird </item>
        <item>Joe Namath </item>
        <item>Michael Phelps </item>
        <item>John Wooden </item>
        <item>Lance Armstrong </item>
        <item>Phil Jackson </item>
        <item>Joe Paterno </item>
        <item>William A. Ward </item>
        <item>Satchel Paige </item>
        <item>Venus Williams </item>
        <item>Babe Ruth </item>
        <item>Evander Holyfield </item>
        <item>Muhammad Ali </item>
        <item>Pat Riley </item>
        <item>Jack Dempsey </item>
        <item>Yogi Berra </item>
        <item>Mike Ditka </item>
        <item>Jim Valvano </item>
        <item>Wayne Gretzky </item>
        <item>Wayne Gretzky </item>
        <item>Dan Gable </item>
        <item>Michael Jordan </item>
        <item>Vince Lombardi </item>
        <item>Joe Rogan </item>
        <item>Joe Rogan </item>
        <item>Joe Rogan </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Tech Quotes-->
    <string-array name="tech_quotes">
        <item>No doubt one may quote history to support any cause, as the devil quotes scripture. </item>
        <item>"It has become appallingly obvious that our technology has exceeded our humanity." </item>
        <item>"A lot of companies have chosen to downsize, and maybe that was the right thing for them. We chose a different path. Our belief was that if we kept putting great products in front of customers, they would continue to open their wallets." </item>
        <item>"I do not fear computers. I fear lack of them." </item>
        <item>"Imagination is more important than knowledge. For knowledge is limited, whereas imagination embraces the entire world, stimulating progress, giving birth to evolution." </item>
        <item>"We have to stop optimizing for programmers and start optimizing for users." </item>
        <item>"Never trust a computer you can\'t throw out a window." </item>
        <item>"Everything is designed. Few things are designed well." </item>
        <item>"The world won't care about your self-esteem. The world will expect you to accomplish something BEFORE you feel good about yourself." </item>
        <item>"Simplicity is about subtracting the obvious and adding the meaningful." </item>
        <item>The most technologically efficient machine that man has ever invented is the book. </item>
        <item>Just because something doesn\'t do what you planned it to do doesn\'t mean it\'s useless. </item>
        <item>It has become appallingly obvious that our technology has exceeded our humanity. </item>
        <item>One machine can do the work of fifty ordinary men. No machine can do the work of one extraordinary man. </item>
        <item>Technology is a word that describes something that doesn\'t work yet. </item>
        <item>All this modern technology just makes people try to do everything at once. </item>
        <item>We are stuck with technology when what we really want is just stuff that works. </item>
        <item>Humanity is acquiring all the right technology for all the wrong reasons. </item>
        <item>It\'s supposed to be automatic, but actually you have to push this button. </item>
        <item>Books may look like nothing more than words on a page, but they are actually an infinitely complex imaginotransference technology that translates odd, inky squiggles into pictures inside your head. </item>
        <item>I think that novels that leave out technology misrepresent life as badly as Victorians misrepresented life by leaving out sex. </item>
        <item>Technological progress has merely provided us with more efficient means for going backwards. </item>
        <item>The human spirit must prevail over technology. </item>
        <item>Technology… the knack of so arranging the world that we don\'t have to experience it. </item>
        <item>Technology frightens me to death. It\'s designed by engineers to impress other engineers. And they always come with instruction booklets that are written by engineers for other engineers — which is why almost no technology ever works. </item>
        <item>The great myth of our times is that technology is communication. </item>
        <item>Technology made large populations possible; large populations now make technology indispensable. </item>
        <item>Computers are useless. They can only give you answers. </item>
        <item>TV and the Internet are good because they keep stupid people from spending too much time out in public. </item>
        <item>This is the whole point of technology. It creates an appetite for immortality on the one hand. It threatens universal extinction on the other. Technology is lust removed from nature. </item>
        <item>The greatest achievement of humanity is not its works of art, science, or technology, but the recognition of its own dysfunction. </item>
        <item>First we thought the PC was a calculator. Then we found out how to turn numbers into letters with ASCII — and we thought it was a typewriter. Then we discovered graphics, and we thought it was a television. With the World Wide Web, we\'ve realized it\'s a brochure. </item>
        <item>Communications tools don\'t get socially interesting until they get technologically boring. </item>
        <item>Any sufficiently advanced technology is equivalent to magic. </item>
        <item>Ethics change with technology. </item>
        <item>So much technology, so little talent. </item>
        <item>Programs must be written for people to read, and only incidentally for machines to execute. </item>
        <item>For a list of all the ways technology has failed to improve the quality of life, please press three. </item>
        <item>As a technology, the book is like a hammer. That is to say, it is perfect: a tool ideally suited to its task. Hammers can be tweaked and varied but will never go obsolete. Even when builders pound nails by the thousand with pneumatic nail guns, every household needs a hammer. </item>
        <item>The ultimate promise of technology is to make us master of a world that we command by the push of a button. </item>
        <item>Technology is the campfire around which we tell our stories. </item>
        <item>The real danger is not that computers will begin to think like men, but that men will begin to think like computers. </item>
        <item>Once a new technology rolls over you, if you\'re not part of the steamroller, you\'re part of the road. </item>
        <item>Hardware: the parts of a computer that can be kicked, but still work. Be like hardware. </item>
        <item>The real problem is not whether machines think but whether men do. </item>
        <item>Technology presumes there\'s just one right way to do things and there never is. </item>
        <item>Getting information off the Internet is like taking a drink from a fire hydrant. </item>
        <item>If we continue to develop our technology without wisdom or prudence, our servant may prove to be our executioner. </item>
        <item>Technology has to be invented or adopted. </item>
        <item>Technology… is a queer thing. It brings you great gifts with one hand, and it stabs you in the back with the other. </item>
        <item>Computers are like bikinis. They save people a lot of guesswork. </item>
        <item>The art challenges the technology, and the technology inspires the art. </item>
        <item>All of our technology is completely unnecessary to a happy life. </item>
        <item>Technology is a useful servant but a dangerous master. </item>
        <item>Technology is anything that wasn\'t around when you were born. </item>
        <item>Science and technology revolutionize our lives, but memory, tradition and myth frame our response. </item>
        <item>Technology is nothing. What\'s important is that you have a faith in people, that they\'re basically good and smart, and if you give them tools, they\'ll do wonderful things with them. </item>
        <item>This is why I loved technology: if you used it right, it could give you power and privacy. </item>
        <item>Please, no matter how we advance technologically, please don\'t abandon the book. There is nothing in our material world more beautiful than the book. </item>
        <item>Technology is teaching us to be human again. </item>
        <item>“I have not failed. I\'ve just found 10,000 ways that won\'t work.” </item>
        <item>“What new technology does is create new opportunities to do a job that customers want done.” </item>
        <item>“Technology like art is a soaring exercise of the human imagination.” </item>
        <item>“Let\'s go invent tomorrow instead of worrying about what happened yesterday.” </item>
        <item>“The great growling engine of change – technology.” </item>
        <item>“Innovation is the outcome of a habit, not a random act.” </item>
        <item>“Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic.” </item>
        <item>“The technology you use impresses no one. The experience you create with it is everything.” </item>
        <item>“It\'s not that we use technology, we live technology.” </item>
        <item>“Once a new technology rolls over you, if you\'re not part of the steamroller, you\'re part of the road.” </item>
        <item>“Technology is best when it brings people together.” </item>
        <item>“Technology is a useful servant but a dangerous master.” </item>
        <item>“The real problem is not whether machines think but whether men do.” </item>
        <item>“Technology is nothing. What\'s important is that you have a faith in people, that they\'re basically good and smart, and if you give them tools, they\'ll do wonderful things with them.” </item>
        <item>“Technology should improve your life… not become your life.” </item>
        <item>“Technology is just a tool. In terms of getting the kids working together and motivating them, the teacher is the most important.” </item>
        <item>“Modern technology has become a total phenomenon for civilization, the defining force of a new social order in which efficiency is no longer an option but a necessity imposed on all human activity.” </item>
        <item>“Our business is about technology, yes. But it\'s also about operations and customer relationships.” </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tech_author">
        <item>Learned Hand </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs </item>
        <item>Isaac Asimov </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Jeff Atwood </item>
        <item>Steve Wozniak </item>
        <item>Brian Reed </item>
        <item>Bill Gates </item>
        <item>John Maeda </item>
        <item>Northrop Frye </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Elbert Hubbard </item>
        <item>Douglas Adams </item>
        <item>Bill Watterson </item>
        <item>Douglas Adams </item>
        <item>R. Buckminster Fuller </item>
        <item>John Brunner </item>
        <item>Jasper Fforde </item>
        <item>Kurt Vonnegut </item>
        <item>Aldous Huxley </item>
        <item>Albert Einstein </item>
        <item>Max Frisch </item>
        <item>John Cleese </item>
        <item>Libby Larsen </item>
        <item>Joseph Wood Krutch </item>
        <item>Pablo Picasso </item>
        <item>Douglas Coupland </item>
        <item>Don DeLillo </item>
        <item>Eckhart Tolle </item>
        <item>Douglas Adams </item>
        <item>Clay Shirky </item>
        <item>Sir Arthur C. Clarke </item>
        <item>Larry Niven </item>
        <item>Vernor Vinge </item>
        <item>Harold Abelson </item>
        <item>Alice Kahn </item>
        <item>James Gleick </item>
        <item>Volker Grassmuck </item>
        <item>Laurie Anderson </item>
        <item>Sydney J. Harris </item>
        <item>Stewart Brand </item>
        <item>Jeff Pesis </item>
        <item>B.F. Skinner </item>
        <item>Robert M. Pirsig </item>
        <item>Mitchell Kapor </item>
        <item>Omar N. Bradley </item>
        <item>Jared Diamond </item>
        <item>Carrie Snow </item>
        <item>Sam Ewing </item>
        <item>John Lasseter </item>
        <item>Tom Hodgkinson </item>
        <item>Christian Lous Lange </item>
        <item>Alan Kay </item>
        <item>Arthur M. Schlesinger </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs </item>
        <item>Cory Doctorow </item>
        <item>Patti Smith </item>
        <item>Simon Mainwaring </item>
        <item>Thomas Edison </item>
        <item>Tim O\'Reilly </item>
        <item>Daniel Bell </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs </item>
        <item>Alvin Toffler </item>
        <item>Sukant Ratnakar </item>
        <item>Arthur C. Clarke </item>
        <item>Sean Gerety </item>
        <item>Godfrey Reggio </item>
        <item>Stewart Brand </item>
        <item>Matt Mullenweg </item>
        <item>Christian Lous Lange </item>
        <item>B.F. Skinner </item>
        <item>Steve Jobs </item>
        <item>Billy Cox </item>
        <item>Bill Gates </item>
        <item>Jacques Ellul </item>
        <item>Michael Dell </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>

